kevczy: Sup George hotz
cIvIcbooks: Yo
codevisionary: hey george
aerotone: windows eww
kruger3117: Ayy
Harm133: Pog
mrgh0st0: CoolStoryBob
knilecrack: wsuppp
zenkai_oogway: PogChamp
foxubu: George o/
Quev1337: yes
dkingdoms: yooo
kruger3117: OwO
smokingbud: yass
javadragoniv: we missed u, u crazy bastard <3
yousef19961: Wsupppppp
nlztw: yes we can
filipenunooliveira: Hi from Portugal
jamesred2313: Windows Kek
jrubenoide: Yes
mkdrmnd: welcome back george
codevisionary: yes I can hear your voice audio
th3_maj0r: We can hear you
erichtp: Yes
dekassssss: hi
foxubu: Windows? Woow
Xandoo: HeyGuys
Gentris: Finally...
zenkai_oogway: yes
jamesred2313: Windows 10 kekekekek
zenkai_oogway: we can hear you
JohnnyWangPepega: yooooo george whats up!
kelvin99: yes
filipenunooliveira: Yes
kruger3117: Yup
yousef19961: Yes
Zasuslive: Hi
knilecrack: no instagram please
Nubadoxd: GeoHotz is really hot ashlolLick ashlolWaifu ashlolLick ashlolWaifu ashlolLick ashlolWaifu ashlolLick ashlolWaifu ashlolLick
foxubu: Your voice has echo
Scrumilation: windows?
erichtp: HELL YEA NO MORE LAG
th3_maj0r: omg this quality george
trader_f: not anymore IMAC PepeHands
dbroers: Yes
nlztw: sick
knilecrack: fuck yeah
Nubadoxd: Inception Hotz incept me ashlolBad
tanoshiizo: legal PogChamp
Cube_Is_Life20: qira for windows when?
capsimirhd: holyyy
dorkmo: windows10 lol
adamalex16: yo
data_day_life: it's crispy as fuck
ainschtain: yo george watsup
jimmyadaro: omg legal windows
funwayz: WE ARE LEGAL
er_ricotta: HOLLA HERMANOOO
kevczy: Why are you using windows
jamesred2313: Windows 10 is free
aerotone: PogChamp
codevisionary: try linux
jimmyadaro: why windows tho
adamalex16: making a game?
zenkai_oogway: @georgehotz Did you see the new windows terminal ad?
mondeverest: bogaEdna bogaEdna bogaEdna
kevczy: Ok good
no_step_on_snek_: 720p? :/
the_middle: Hello world!
mondeverest: bogaFirewall bogaFirewall bogaFirewall
eyep1e: windows?
Nubadoxd: Use kali noob CoolStoryBob
jimmyadaro: omg ls in windows
data_day_life: you have to enable *nix support
Zasuslive: Learn UE4 not unity!
jimmyadaro: how about ls -latr?
knilecrack: yeah
Scrumilation: No, the actual new terminal, you ahve to compile it yourself or some shit
kelvin99: unity ml do it please
zimxtv: What do you think about Uber going IPO this month
knilecrack: you can install wsl bro
aerotone: no its fine
markovchain21: Hello :) it is an honor. i just finished the 10hour slam stream
foxubu: Install wsl
flovvvvv: hi
adamalex16: pp mode
knilecrack: welcome :)
aathove: hey dude
jamesred2313: Windows crashed
Duschjenkovic: xDD
foxubu: Stream stopped?
emi1ie: emi1ie subscribed with Twitch Prime.
markovchain21: Hello :) it is an honor. i just finished the 10hour slam stream. <3
hoffs: much better
Nubadoxd: @georgehotz daddy the stueam is gone ashlolOhNo ashlolBulbathump ashlolBulbathump
acheesedanish00: uping the resolution
capsimirhd: lmao
kevczy: Stopped
xyrtha: How did you learn to code ?
mrgh0st0: Blue Screen
deR_Ed: insta celeb waow
bpostalci: What happened
xyrtha: do you have tricks ? ;p
Johnnymamen: refresh stream
menchedanem: windows power
kevczy: Crashed
foxubu: George exploded lol
javadragoniv: meh quality, camera is not really nice lol
kevczy: George your stream crashed
flovvvvv: you cool
J3rwin: Your good
billymack: does anyone know which keyboard he uses?
th3_maj0r: He didn't chrash
avagyannarek: Duude we missed you
knilecrack: :D
aathove: @billymack hhkb 2
flovvvvv: woww
tanoshiizo: PogChamp
th3_maj0r: refresh guys
UniversalGeneve: noice
Scrumilation: LMAO
LazDays: LUL
adamalex16: saxy
J3rwin: ...the fuck
codevisionary: OMG
knilecrack: rofl
smurfd0: no, 238 .. crisp
dorkmo: lol
tanoshiizo: who's this guy? PogChamp
Chris_XIX: WOAH
konradcho: hahah
funwayz: ??????
FartKnockGomez: the future! PogChamp
avagyannarek: DAAAAAMN
trader_f: LMao
jdquintana: Happy Hacking Keyboard
zenkai_oogway: PogChamp
nlztw: haHAA
Nubadoxd: @georgehotz you're 2 much to handle ashlolCool
Aerdeyne: PogU
FartKnockGomez: @tanoshiizo dude is a straight up genius
ranjaman: wtf
J3rwin: FeelsWeirdMan
no_step_on_snek_: haha damn
jamesred2313: Is that a Zuckerberg meme
kelvin99: cool stuff
kevczy: Crashed
purpbroccoli: very fashionable
yousef19961: Lol
flovvvvv: ahahah
HanksPlay: i want to see you walk outside with this
tanoshiizo: diy? PogChamp
LazDays: PogChamp
HanksPlay: WALK OUTSIDE WITH IT
yoyo_brobro: YEEET
HanksPlay: lol
nmuntz_: I was really starting to miss your streams dude!
konradcho: like alien from rick and morty
FartKnockGomez: geohotz is the shit
UniversalGeneve: LUL
markovchain21: i just have a LeapMotion
jamesred2313: No
msjuck: hey dude
Nubadoxd: @georgehotz that's 2 much, I can't handle it Kreygasm
Dimendz: I finally caught a live stream Pog
knilecrack: is it working on that laptop ?
funwayz: Some matrix shit
Cube_Is_Life20: fuck wires
mondeverest: i take 4
veomx: Hi George
austin_1_2: @hanksplay he hasn’t been outside in years Kappa
nightknight0000: new house?
WoockieCookiee: hey @georgehotz still CEO Comma.ai?
myaocat: i thought you was going to buy macbook
HanksPlay: HanksPlay subscribed with Twitch Prime.
kevczy: George your stream crasheddd
knilecrack: I thought u need better config for that
jamesred2313: Refresh the stream
Bombapil0t: 10k followers gg wp
aathove: can you check your balls temperature on it
J3rwin: would people beat me up if you wear one of those and go outside.
knilecrack: like really good GPU 1070
knilecrack: ahhaha
HanksPlay: congrats on the new office btw
UniversalGeneve: is comma ai dead? was waiting for you guys to hit L4 first
nlztw: u look dope dude
Bombapil0t: futuremen
kelvin99: would love to see walk t0mcr00se in this AR headset
yoyo_brobro: why cant i donate
FartKnockGomez: real version tony stark LUL
Zasuslive: George how we gonna hack the simulation
Protoxus: VR is the future jgrTARD
myaocat: congrats i thought you hate office but your in office all day
alxhotel: Where do you work ?
veomx: simulation in a simulation. r&m
mehi9h: I hope ur not switching to win
Scrumilation: that looks like some shit kim kardashian would wear
Cube_Is_Life20: fuck wires I wanna take that shit around
aathove: auction your keyboard
WoockieCookiee: i dont know why u arent CEO
acheesedanish00: George is gonna prove the simulation by making another simulation
jxeus: you look like a nerd
FartKnockGomez: lady gaga wants one to go with her dress
th3_maj0r: 1m2019.com
Bombapil0t: what the heck
kevczy: I’ll pay 10,000for that keyboard
codevisionary: that's why you should be using linux @georgehotz
UniversalGeneve: so is the camera on that modular? seems detachable. it would be nice if its a tack-on to regular glasses
veomx: where are you george
alxhotel: Instagram
Zasuslive: million subs on insta?
data_day_life: 1 million followers on IG
Bombapil0t: get big o ninsta
knilecrack: thre is no dream
dorkmo: instagram
HanksPlay: get instagram famous
dbroers: I’d pay $2000 for that keyboard
trader_f: 1M follo on IG
FartKnockGomez: wireless quality vr?
aathove: just bot your insta
myaocat: pewdiepie?
Nubadoxd: @georgehotz this is the equivalent of a cowboy hat, in the hotness mesure, 10/10 all the puss you can get Kreygasm
markovchain21: i think i finally found out how to exploit our simulation @georgehotz
Protoxus: @veomx T H E C L O U D
dbroers: Instagram
kevczy: Instagram celebrity!!!!
th3_maj0r: ahaha
grootdoloot: <3 <3 <3 <3
smokingbud: i can legit send you 1m followers @georgehotz
Dqyijote: omg new computer :O :O :O
capsimirhd: lool
nlztw: jerk off 2 times twice is a dream
Goooshlrific: literally anything else porbably
jamesred2313: Why don't you use brave browser?
eyep1e: 1m followers insta dream
flovvvvv: George you awesome
HanksPlay: YEAH i want to see those IG thots in Virtual Reality
aathove: why are you learning unity??
Dimendz: What are the specs on your new pc?
th3_maj0r: instagram will remove public likes number George
ISD_Schogol: Whats better for insta then AR? You should get some titties :D
myaocat: did you try the new terminal on windows?
Nubadoxd: Call Jabril Kappa
kevczy: Omg
codevisionary: don't worry george, you're better at coding than all of us here
Zasuslive: can we talk about the simulation later or something at least
trader_f: 10K ANDY Pog
adamalex16: just followed
kevczy: Dude I’ll teach you unity seriously
dbroers: You just need a gold necklace
knilecrack: it's not out yet, the terminal
mehdirussel05: happy ramadan
tybutnowyoudie: did you move to san diego?
ranjaman: lets hack things
Harm133: what language
HanksPlay: yes he did
kevczy: Would you text me back in instagram
Bombapil0t: windows ffs
myaocat: c#
nanodanger7: nanodanger7 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 12 months, currently on a 12 month streak! 1 year lol
th3_maj0r: https://www.instagram.com/georgehotz/
grootdoloot: #hacktheworld
Zasuslive: learn Unreal Engine 4 not unity :))))
Adolfich77: karmikS karmikRaid cmonBruh
Nubadoxd: Only follow if I can get some Lorno in the IG story's TheThing
aathove: pee or poo, which is the best?
myaocat: you create unity programs with c# or c but
adamalex16: ue4 is a fucking power house
KtothePop: WutFace headset
FartKnockGomez: stream from the future PogChamp
knilecrack: start pwershell windows btn i or A
veomx: how much is one of this
cccnrd: fancy profile pic
knilecrack: x 1*
zoloviski: unreal engine dude is much better
Dimendz: Use source engine :(
poopboy7: VR Hentai game ? PogChamp
yoyo_brobro: yoyo_brobro subscribed at Tier 1.
kevczy: Is it gonna be vr?
Harm133: C# is awesome Pog
LazDays: wut c# PogChamp
adamalex16: well heavy but if u wanna make a killer game go to cry engine that is a fucking unit m8
myaocat: oof
cccnrd: wooow northstar?
Zasuslive: why unity m8 use unreal engine
zimxtv: Is pixetech his new company?
knilecrack: windows x and I
knilecrack: that's all you need
FartKnockGomez: seems legit
tanoshiizo: so anime is real now?
cccnrd: prototype from u or leap?
Acles123: techwear
Adolfich77: is this guy is tesla auto pilot killer?
cjaynowski: PYRAMID SCHEME
trader_f: Shopify 4Head
tanoshiizo: LUL
aathove: you're on coke right??
trader_f: RICH POG
Bombapil0t: TriHard
myaocat: we cant see the glasses
nlztw: FUNgineer FUNgineer FUNgineer
SpecialAgentSkye: Pog
baymer1: Do you think real time tracking will come soon enough to make AR relevant?
Toaster_PG: lmfaooo
CoffeeD2: how the fk are u not rich already? lol
Bloodspark_: LUL
veomx: with sugar
UniversalGeneve: SeemsGood SeemsGood
J3rwin: FeelsWeirdMan
cccnrd: ar overrated
KtothePop: 200 grams of adderall ? D:
rattata400: AR? :P
myaocat: did you try the new windows terminal????
psYch0maD: You seem to happy for not being drugged
dorkmo: B-12
Dimendz: What processor and gpu are you running?
Bloodspark_: lol
rattata400: what is AR?
rattata400: :P
Duschjenkovic: LUL
Dqyijote: pls hacking nasa u re the best
veomx: pls tell hehe
knilecrack: it's all good
Bloodspark_: you're so hype
Bombapil0t: :)
zenkai_oogway: Kappa
trader_f: Kapp
740ii: normal people always think you're high as hell
markovchain21: i saw a pic on Instagram, where he played the beta version of beeing rich with a new BMW @georgehotz
Bloodspark_: hyper*
jamesred2313: We trust you brah
myaocat: you arent rich because you quit working on google. you said because of being office but you are sitting on office. trust no one
Bloodspark_: new pc? :o
gl3nn_wolf3: George your back !
Bloodspark_: RAZER OFC LUL
J3rwin: You have 300 viewers already? what did you do
gl3nn_wolf3: we love you
KtothePop: RAZER OMEGALUL
brevan04: The real George Hotz got a windows!?! FAKENEWS
kevczy: Weed temperature lol
codevisionary: dude he's ready to program, and has 300 viewers. Of course he's hype
Chris_XIX: How often do you go live tho? That's what I wanna know if I subscribe
yellingdog: yellingdog subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Kvann1 : PogChamp
cccnrd: prototype from u or from leap directly? we are trying to build a northdstar at our interaction design course
Mac_33: Are you becoming an AR boy?
UniversalGeneve: UniversalGeneve subscribed at Tier 1.
tybutnowyoudie: PogChamp
Zasuslive: who cares it does the job it needs to
Dimendz: Fair enough
rattata400: dont show activation code
dxxdpools: Why windows?
baymer1: Isn't AR kinda weak cause of poor real-time tracking? How much longer until it's gooood
stale2000: PogChamp
veomx: you welcome your new subscriber?
ISD_Schogol: 1800?? O_o
aerotone: monka
brevan04: Drive car with VR
myaocat: why didn't you buy i10 cpu?
cccnrd: why pixie? what does it mean?
J3rwin: Razer wat
dxxdpools: You putting Ubuntu on that?
cccnrd: cringe name
foxubu: What are we going to learn today? :)
veomx: how much for one?
dbroers: Shoulda got the Dell XPS
NolanBridges: @veomx $599
Mac_33: I know some people who work at the company who developed the lens system for the HoloLens
cccnrd: love u bb
veomx: ah thx :)
ArfArf: hi
dbroers: It’s too big though
codevisionary: hire me @georgehotz . I want to build your website for pixetech
brevan04: Eye tracking?
KtothePop: FOV Kreygasm
myaocat: pixie like pixel animations
foxubu: What are we going to learn today? :)
NolanBridges: @foxubu Unity
redbullwiiings: dont get started on FOV Kreygasm
myaocat: united nations
brevan04: Will it have eye tracking? Good eye tracking is worth $$$ in research
Bullanguerock: HYPE
alxhotel: pixie like in pixel 3a is the best phone
foxubu: @nolanbridges Okay, let’s code :D
Zasuslive: its easy
Mac_33: You should watch this before you drink more La Croix: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vx9VRdtio7E
baymer1: Damn, recognizing AR needs improvements to be actually enjoyable is a huuge step, I'm excited for Pixie Tech
J3rwin: does he create companies every time he streams
myaocat: geo did you try the new windows terminal??
ranjaman: sounds good to me
Bloodspark_: Pog
CaptainAshtar: hey @georgehotz good to see you online
Dimendz: Learning is the fun stuff, go for it don't be worried.
dorkmo: <html><body>buy pixie</body></html>
s4ngim3d: hello
cccnrd: @brevan04 eye tracking overrated mouse tracking is betta
onu4r: dude we missed you
ISD_Schogol: In b4 sued by nigerian company Pixie Technologies Kappa
cccnrd: just use unity and done
onu4r: where were you
yellingdog: no emotes yet? what is this a twitch chat for noobs?
HanksPlay: Hey George, how long this stream is going to be? because im going to lunch but i want to watch everything
myaocat: did you see the new windows terminal???
cccnrd: join the northstar discourd, nice community
UniversalGeneve: push an MVP and connect with SF insta ppl = more $100 in your pocket(s). i feel like an MVP should be enough. like real-time environment snapchat filter tech kinda stuff. (P.S. not trying to backseat, just genuinely interested in this)
stale2000: PepeHands What about 999 mode in OS class? PepeHands Does that not count as game programming?
brevan04: Dead Reckoning
kevczy: I’ll pay u as a tutor 5000 dollars
HanksPlay: PokPikachu
brevan04: Fake news
ranjaman: don't you using a mechanical keyboard ?
Bombapil0t: magic magic
brevan04: Dont do stupid looking animation
myaocat: ar isnt new.. snapchat doing it
HanksPlay: the video is too loud and i cant hear you
kevczy: The user interface is reallybD tho
J3rwin: so "hardcore"
trader_f: Do a Woman can suck my d pls Kreygasm
CheeseburgerB: :)
claymorehack1: hey man what's up
trader_f: TRUE
HanksPlay: true
CheeseburgerB: f
crusher_az: lol
trader_f: fuck this shit
kevczy: Lol
Zasuslive: its clearly fakezzzzz
myaocat: you are scam
robinduckett: HTC Vive has the same deal
kevczy: Dude tho if you don’t even have few thousand bus...
dbroers: Agreed
myaocat: stop throwing fake news
CheeseburgerB: LUL
robinduckett: I'm paying £30 odd a month for my Vive
tybutnowyoudie: LUL
veomx: what you think about oculus rift?
nlztw: LUL
Dimendz: For me AR won't be worth it until I can't tell I'm using it lol
UniversalGeneve: PWNED
trader_f: Lmao
J3rwin: OMEGALUL
Acles123: LUL
rhytual: LUL
joiput: LUL
KtothePop: LUL
brevan04: Lol
knilecrack: ahaha
Bloodspark_: LUL
flovvvvv: lol
Rlchibi: LUL
kevczy: Lol
thesidjway: LUL
CaptainAshtar: wtf that's insane
2bumbum: LUL
pyythonn: lol
crusher_az: LUL
slimpimp007: lmao
nlztw: yee, right
JBirch10: quality and functionality
Bombapil0t: :D
brevan04: Show off hardware
SanyBarbie: Hahahah! Legend!!
andrex_andrex: FortOne FortOne FortOne
skinzo1998: !time
Dimendz: 3 billion dollars and that's what they come through with?
dorkmo: shipability!
Roudkill: Aw shit, here we go...
knilecrack: don't u need vs for unity?
SpecialAgentSkye: Will you be able to capture what you see through the ar headset? @georgehotz
KtothePop: TRACK PAD LUL
cesaaron88: Here we go agane
knilecrack: windwos btn arrow to fix windows
codevisionary: A professional website design is key to marketing whatever it is you're trying to sell, whether or not you have a Shopify. @georgehotz If your site looks good, the product your selling looks good, it will sell more. Plain and simple. Hire me, please?
kevczy: Vs is free
JBirch10: get a mouse you barbarian lol
J3rwin: "Im new to windows"
cromize: cromize subscribed with Twitch Prime.
myaocat: i dont think its nice to trash on company. why dont you trash about apple and their prices? did magic leap do something to you or are you trying to compete them..
Zasuslive: george doesnt need a nice website to sell
kevczy: C# is really ez
Mac_33: @myaocat You just contradicted yourself.
CaptainAshtar: @georgehotz what is this windows now?
robinduckett: first mistake
saulgd: trackpad and laptop keyboard NotLikeThis
Bombapil0t: collecting data Kreygasm
Risx: Risx subscribed with Twitch Prime.
J3rwin: LOL
SpecialAgentSkye: OG jailbreaker. Dont bash!
virgoshlok: hi!
hoffs: debt is part of american dream
myaocat: would you mind if soneone trash on comma ai?
smurfd0: you get what you pay for .. :)
myaocat: Tesla is doing better
o_sagga: you're awesome man
JBirch10: YES WE ARE
rhytual: no pressure Kappa
aerotone: PogChamp content
onu4r: you would be a great sales guy
fjeuber: Mate I have 128 gigs of ram do u even try xddddddddfdddddddddddd
Zasuslive: its 10x easier than the stuff you've done in the past
Cube_Is_Life20: qira for windows when?
saulgd: @georgehotz are you using WSL?
Bombapil0t: not yet ^^
Dieun: I heard this guy is master game dev
codevisionary: check out Magic Leap's website @georgehotz. I bet the product design and branding play a key role in whatever sales it has.
igorovich: windows SwiftRage
J3rwin: something tells me you will be at the end of this stream
o_sagga: get a second screen!
tybutnowyoudie: comparing commaai to tesla FailFish
CaptainAshtar: owww that will be amazing to watch :) i'll get the popcorn
robinduckett: Apple has financing too ffs
Nesquik80: @georgehotz why windows?
myaocat: @cube_is_life20 he didnt test it but you can try
elfacu00: will this be reuploaded?
flovvvvv: Uniti so simple for you
p0pmart: G E O H O T B O I S
SpecialAgentSkye: Unity UX Pepega
th3_maj0r: Cam bottom right would be probably better with this editor
CheeseburgerB: F
codermark: Can we except a new AR glasses from you? ;)
BilgehanB2: !uptime
knilecrack: ahahaha
KtothePop: F
JBirch10: get a mobile external monitor for your laptop
Bloodspark_: LUL
FargioFarmani: F
Zasuslive: do unreal engine instead!?
Bombapil0t: fml
purpbroccoli: Unity setup stream
Infinitelym: rip
dorkmo: unity upgrade streammmm
igorovich: specs of pc???
seanxedge: F
Zasuslive: Why not use Unreal Engine/!?!
mehi9h: mega F
Dqyijote: omg poor guy
o_sagga: F
Dimendz: I do think unreal engine would be much better for AR
CaptainAshtar: :D love it mental...
SpecialAgentSkye: NotLikeThis Y UNITY YYYYY
d0neall: LULW
alxhotel: F
robinduckett: lol I wanted you
saulgd: NotLikeThis
J3rwin: F
o_sagga: get a second screen!
surfNsmurf: Hack something instead, let's see that SSH wizard
Toaster_PG: omega lul
imageliner: F
robinduckett: warned *
cesaaron88: setup stream Kreygasm
funwayz: 420 haHAA
cccnrd: boiiRollt boiiRollt boiiRollt
fimonlark: why you choose unity instead of ue4
seanxedge: Unityhub makes everything easier :D
myaocat: did you look on windows terminal? i think you will like it
CheeseburgerB: NotLikeThis
allthesm0ke: "burj khalifa cost to build" are we the same person hotz...?
robinduckett: mistake two
cccnrd: unity is better for noob
Kvann1 : Blender PogChamp
aerotone: dont show ur id WTF
cccnrd: what did u verify!!!
codevisionary: oh no, you just showed your drivers license
KtothePop: @georgehotz you could do some jumping jacks while its installing PogChamp
asherism: KYC? you buying crypto?
MatiGoG: just get godot LULW
Nesquik80: @georgehotz why windows?
zimxtv: Ur license bro
Dimendz: just get unreal engine
SpecialAgentSkye: PogChamp ITS DOWNLOADING
keepingtrckofthisacct: you back! @georgehotz
saulgd: nice 3rd world internet speed LUL
c19946: open that pic showing id please
duzy: too small 2 read
Zasuslive: go for unreal engine
Staredad: Hey geohot
tornyl: is it laptop?
benjibanjobenjo: DOWNLOAD t90Hype
smokingbud: speedtest?
myaocat: why cant you just apt-get install unity KappaClaus
Bombapil0t: razer blade?
robinduckett: it's not like we don't know who he is
Acles123: do you know c#?
Cube_Is_Life20: hey George does zerodium actually pay out?
FargioFarmani: preread the tutorial
gofoboso: why waste time on creating games?
imageliner: I want ti see the download Kappa
HanksPlay: show us your chrome history
pyythonn: unreal engine is where its at
KyleUE: why unity?
cccnrd: dont do this
cccnrd: just directly build ur project
myaocat: this will be fun to watch
PabloBree: I'm pretty sure that in less than a month, you will learn unity completly @georgehotz
SpecialAgentSkye: sudo apt-get install unityhub
tornyl: @georgehotz is it laptop?
virgoshlok: unity vs unreal which one should a beginner learn??
eyep1e: @georgehotz stream more man i miss this
onu4r: @georgehotz give me ssh access
Trenz2: Hey :D
cccnrd: F
SpecialAgentSkye: F
NolanBridges: @tornyl it is laptop
robinduckett: can't apt get on a Windows machine
Kvann1 : F
Bloodspark_: f
asherism: F
Bullanguerock: F
1Riaxma: F
coaker30: F
veebii: F
fimonlark: F
pyythonn: f
Zasuslive: This is a good opportunity to see how georges brain breaks down a new field/industry
myaocat: f
acheesedanish00: f
Cube_Is_Life20: F
benjibanjobenjo: <f
codevisionary: @georgehotz stream everyday, you can become a twitch partner and get $$$$$
zimxtv: F
veomx: we have two hours time difference? lol
Kvann1 : F - Fix cam BlessRNG
inspectorrr: f
Zasuslive: or how he learns to use a new application ..
Bloodspark_: I thought it said failed istead of nailed LUL
J3rwin: Just stream everyday lol 4Head
jellyjar: oh wow a windows pc?
alluxua: what he is trying to code?
fumundaqueso: maybe he sliced his neck shaving and doesnt want you to see
kevczy: Yea what are you up to nowadays?
tybutnowyoudie: can you move your cam?
Zasuslive: he is learning Unity3D
keepingtrckofthisacct: with your skills, you should dm streamers: handmadehero (casey) or naysayer88(johnathan blow) @georgehotz
Kvann1 : Fix cam BlessRNG @georgehotz
myaocat: f
acheesedanish00: f
KyleUE: why are you learning unity?
Zasuslive: he is getting into AR
riddari_: holy shit
gofoboso: yeah why?
crusher_az: lol
riddari_: I finally caught a geohot stream
J3rwin: he 3d printed that
WizWiz0: why not Unreal?
saulgd: can you do the whole strim with that thing on your face LUL
alluxua: That is pretty adorable
Bloodspark_: windows ding
google_cat: D:
alxhotel: Why Windows ?
aathove: you need a gaming headset to be a real streamer
cccnrd: where will u get your display driver from???
Dimendz: Any reason you went with Unity over ue4?
keepingtrckofthisacct: @riddari_ i know, right?!
eyep1e: fooken windows
kevczy: What is that green called?
HanksPlay: developers get pixie for free?
SpecialAgentSkye: Cam little lower? We done gone looked at top half of your face for 5 minutes LUL Not complaining though, still looking Kreygasm
Zasuslive: probably memory bias, just went with unity just cause
kevczy: Have u gone to any ctf?
pyythonn: prefap
aathove: LUL
codermark: hoping you will make the best AR glasses, I really want one :D
cIvIcbooks: is semantic versioning not a thing anymore? everybody using years in the versions
aathove: where's the RGB lighting now that you'
aathove: where's the rgb lighting now you've got a windows pc
avagyannarek: ResidentSleeper
stathizzzz: I dont know about Unity either but would choose Unreal engine I like more playing with C than a pseudo language like C# LUL
wall_streeter: why unity?
alluxua: so geohot is moving from self driving car to gaming industry?
NolanBridges: @aathove agreed, it's a Razer too LUL
keepingtrckofthisacct: I'd suggest Unreal
kevczy: He’s just doing whatever he wants
Zasuslive: AR isnt gaming
aathove: @NolanBridges get a load of George using razer and NO RGB
keepingtrckofthisacct: @stathizzzz
rhytual: @cIvIcbooks you are not a real hipster if you dont version by year
allthesm0ke: RATTED
dxxdpools: Where did he go?
alluxua: By the way, what's AR?
Zasuslive: augmented reality
pentaquant: Hi @georgehotz I'm 27 and in Finance in SF, and it fucking sucks. Do you think its too late to make a pivot to data science or SD?
saulgd: is he a babyface now? Kappa
fjeuber: Augmented Reality
NolanBridges: @aathove look what you did LUL
Bloodspark_: LULW
Bombapil0t: litstuff
saulgd: @pentaquant make your monies and GIT OUT
jellyjar: ah he has a razer blade?
P0LY: LUL
Nesquik80: @georgehotz what razer do you have
aathove: @NolanBridges fuck he's gonna start coding his own keyboard
Bloodspark_: GAMERS haHAA
kevczy: George how about the defcon that is coming up
Dimendz: Do you ever game?
codevisionary: thanks to gamers, us programmers have better hardware @georgehotz
Cihonidas: LUL
JBirch10: You need to understand them with what you are doing now
Dqyijote: Gaymers
UniversalGeneve: @pentaquant bio major in SJ, pivoted to DS/ML, beel loving it
HanksPlay: AND DELETE BLENDER
HanksPlay: download Maya
Toaster_PG: i am gaymer
Darth_Kirias: Hey man, is that a razer laptop? @georgehotz
riddari_: holy shit windows looks fucking hideous
slimyoof: @georgehotz have you tried vr porn? OpieOP
Kvann1 : @HanksPlay DansGame
o_sagga: @georgehotz just finished college, what should I do?
rauluz: have u seen the new windows terminal?
c19946: why u not try using react native ar or sth like that learning c sharp for ar is wasting time
jellyjar: lmao
dxxdpools: Did he say he will be back?
slimyoof: LUL
erichtp: AR porn tho
alluxua: what is vr porn?
saulgd: @georgehotz just came out of the womb what should i do?
rhytual: LUL
Bombapil0t: LUL
Hjorthlol: @riddari_ the fuq u say
pentaquant: @UniversalGeneve how long did it take you to pivot?
raikkonen933: windows ResidentSleeper
stathizzzz: VR what?? PogChamp
riddari_: @Hjorthlol windows sucks
myaocat: till the batteries die
HanksPlay: and LIDAR is a SCAM
TheTastefulToastie: and who wants life amirite?
HanksPlay: lol
codevisionary: AR is the future
Jeppelelle: So, when can we expect a haptic penis sleeve?
stathizzzz: Augmented chicks > virtual chicks, makes sense PogChamp
Jannnik: just create JOI from Bladerunner 2049
Acles123: wait until vr becomes life
markvlk: Do you miss living in your office
aathove: where are the stream snipers
UniversalGeneve: @pentaquant if you have drive, you could do it in a year, it took me 6 months, just taking moocs and doing a lot of relevant projects
trader_f: no more vim
cccnrd: where r u rightnow?
o_sagga: @georgehotz just finished college, what should I do??
kevczy: Unity asset store still sucks
alluxua: game developer
veomx: the cloud hehe
th3_maj0r: @georgehotz http://1m2019.com/ doesn't work
HanksPlay: masturbate
PhelpsGG: @georgehotz I appreciate you and the work you do brother. You're a brilliant mind in a society of mostly stupid people. We need more people like you man. Much love <3
gofoboso: pay your loan :p
cccnrd: learn programming
riddari_: how does one become as good with vim as geohot?
0xBADBADBAD: You should focus on your instagram influencer career.
fumundaqueso: why do you keep chugging an empty soda
mkdrmnd: too late 😂😂😂
asherism: what inspired this new venture or "hustle"??????
HanksPlay: learn python and javascript and get a 6 figures salary =D
revolutionist123: PogChamp
benjibanjobenjo: hack the next playstation and get infamous :)
aathove: yo geo are you gonna move to denver with the new law
saulgd: i'm already thirty NotLikeThis
pentaquant: @UniversalGeneve thats the shit thing about finance, long hours
Bloodspark_: PogChamp
BookRaider: what do oyu mean by sell out?
Dimendz: Be the first person to make VR and AR actually good please.
Cihonidas: life hacker
elonzupsk: Hahaha but you did with comma
veomx: a word
Kvann1 : stop NotLikeThis
Bioaim7: true
Bloodspark_: Nice movie plot LUL
cccnrd: r u feminist?
ApexJnr: @georgehotz americans on reddit told me 25k is low for a web developer at 22 (then i realised that they have no concept of what people make outside of the us ) NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
J3rwin: sellout?
maxviaa: are you using a monitor?
stathizzzz: Unity's ECS model is crap, build a custom ECS model in python that is gonna be 10 times better with less effort than learning Unity PogChamp
erichtp: define selling out
knilecrack: Whats wrong with selling out
o_sagga: thanks man
myaocat: One who betrays a cause for personal advancement.
codevisionary: https://clips.twitch.tv/AbrasiveBashfulGrouseNononoCat
dbroers: Why not make games in the App Store? A lot less risk and work, and you make money.
alluxua: geohot, how about sing a song?
ApexJnr: @georgehotz make a game where u hack ps3
rhytual: @ApexJnr 25k is like the lower boundary for a web dev in central europe
elonzupsk: Real bs hahaha
veomx: i miss your small room
VertXY: Thanks for the advice, just split up
Zasuslive: he doesnt want to become a game developer guys, he wants to create an AR product/platform
JumpTwiice: PogChamp
aathove: you should kickstart it
SgT_Vimes: Sellout!
dbroers: @vertxy lol
codevisionary: you're right @Zasuslive
ApexJnr: @rhytual if you're 22 years old, 25k is fine and you're ahead of most people your age on average XD
Acles123: headset looks like something out of ghost in the shell
myaocat: http://1m2019.com/
elonzupsk: Damn that looks great
HanksPlay: i dont believe in what i do here at google, but i have bills to pay =/
pentaquant: Like private equity.... pure sellout
SpecialAgentSkye: unity LUL
aathove: are you sure there's nothing in the can, you keep drinking from it LUL
elonzupsk: Lets raise seed for that
th3_maj0r: Installing unity is harder than learning unity
Zasuslive: its never too late to switch to UE4 george...
dbroers: Kids...
Zasuslive: ;D
kevczy: What are you drinking
Adolfich77: where is coding??????
ApexJnr: @rhytual i got flamed and they were talking about 80k but then i realised they dont understand
0xBADBADBAD: Imagine getting life advice from a person with that desktop background
lightofhel1: too many reloads ResidentSleeper
asherism: lifestyle creep!!!!
0xBADBADBAD: love you tho
aathove: i buy poo on the deep web LUL
HanksPlay: idk, i like to buy stuff, makes me happier i think
Hiladina: does stream freez for ou guys aswell?
eyep1e: green tea have to live in cali cucks
HanksPlay: idk, im a little empty
Bombapil0t: :D
UniversalGeneve: @pentaquant i was a lab rat - 8 hours a day, plus i had to devote an entire day for taking care of my grandmother. i'm not trying to give you a sob story, but what i'm saying is that if you want it, you'll make time. i was sleeping 4 hours maybe 3-4x a week, just so i could fit my studying in. you can do it, you have a background setup for it, i had to relearn a LOT of math.
JBirch10: Electricity lol and internet, insurance, you know bills lol
data_day_life: !ig
elonzupsk: Hit some angel meetings with that prototype
ApexJnr: @georgehotz ps3 hacking game 2020?
0xBADBADBAD: No.
Bloodspark_: depends on who you are yeah
javadragoniv: gee 800$ where did u find that lol
myaocat: no one is talented like you. no one can hack iphone, create a self driving car under a month..
knilecrack: What if you are happy selling out
eyep1e: wen ps2 hak
revolutionist123: @georgehotz How 1m goal goes?
nanodanger7: @georgehotz this is my 1 year subscriber anniversary any discount? :D
Acles123: true
kevczy: Now you talk like my dad
SpecialAgentSkye: Like in game skins LUL
pentaquant: @UniversalGeneve thats not a sob story thats a fucking motivational story. I'm going to DM you
0xBADBADBAD: What else will I do to fill the void in my soul?
aathove: should i buy poo off the deep web
anthraxvirus322: Any Pepega in chat
aathove: TehePelo
Bloodspark_: Pepega Clap
WaIeed: First time on unity?
SpecialAgentSkye: Should i sub to you for the dopamine rush @georgehotz ? 🤔
rhytual: @ApexJnr its a good starting salary at 22 for sure (guess u are from europe?) - muricans also have a different tax and social system, so the numbers dont rly work that way (ofc SV is a bit different LUL)
Poethick: @georgehotz F2 to rename
davidsit_site: lol
aathove: 4Head
BookRaider: i can sell you high grade poo for $1
kevczy: I’m going out for defcon!
myaocat: nice
aathove: @BookRaider please I need my daily hit of poo
Dimendz: I genuinely think if you want to make the best AR product, unreal engine is the way to go
myaocat: @kevczy who pay?
orochiviia: LUL
youngsachi: PogChamp
Dimendz: ooo PogChamp
kanogger: :)
sharmajee: NotLikeThis
HaywoodJabroni: whats up forsenE
anthraxvirus322: BUT can you put Pepega in unity ?
myaocat: f
kevczy: No pay, it’s gonna be tmrw for ctf
Zasuslive: yh so ease of use = unity
Johnnymamen: any antivirus preinstlled on razeer laptop?
aathove: wait isn't that just blender??
HaywoodJabroni: any bajs forsenE
showzennn: Are you going to be a game develepor now @georgehotz ?
myaocat: @kevczy what team are you?
ZiklarxD: Upcoming gamedeveloper? @georgehotz
JumpTwiice: bajs🔭
HaywoodJabroni: forsen1
Bioaim7: he already is @showzennn
anthraxvirus322: Game developer PogChamp
Dimendz: Need a second monitor lol
myaocat: @kevczy i also play ctf but im really bad at it
smurfd0: kindof like 3d studio or blender
myaocat: maybe i should ditch the lifestyle
anthraxvirus322: just add one more screen 4Head
showzennn: @Bioaim7 what games has he made?
kevczy: I work on reversing
myaocat: i don t know what it even means
th3_maj0r: almost 500 viewers boys
HaywoodJabroni: PogChamp
Hjorthlol: DatSheffy /
anthraxvirus322: PogChamp
HaywoodJabroni: monkaS
youngsachi: PogChamp
Dimendz: PogChamp
alluxua: I like his sweater
HaywoodJabroni: monkaS powerful
kevczy: I’ve won about 3ctf by now
Dimendz: u r god
Bloodspark_: PogChamp
HaywoodJabroni: speshial forsenT
NolanBridges: Dabbing John Lemon
anthraxvirus322: it is alive monkaS
cccnrd: boiiRollt boiiRollt
Bloodspark_: Who is this god? Pog
HanksPlay: i recommend you to go back to T pose
cccnrd: boiiHip boiiHip boiiHip
NolanBridges: @HanksPlay I agree tho
eyep1e: john lemon for potus
anthraxvirus322: FeeldAmazingMan
myaocat: @kevczy did you debug a .net application? i am trying to attach process but cant see locals and i dont know how to resolve it
anthraxvirus322: FeelsAmazingMan
HanksPlay: unity and skeletons are messy
NoneFuture: what's going on guys?
HaywoodJabroni: pajaShrugL forsenE pajaShrugR
HanksPlay: just go back to T pose
showzennn: prefabs implement Composite pattern?
NolanBridges: @nonefuture learning Unity
Kvann1 : Character
anthraxvirus322: just go back to T pose 4Head
HaywoodJabroni: 4Head
NolanBridges: @nonefuture so he can code games for AR I think
gal40: Any node in the hierarchy is a gameobject
NoneFuture: @NolanBridges thanks
gofoboso: getting Boro
gofoboso: boring ×
showzennn: he is going to create a simul
しのし: auto save above scene
woobot: auto save is top right of the scenes
NolanBridges: @gofoboso You know you don't have to watch if you think it's boring...
veomx: hey george you have really a BMW
machinelearningbot: you definitely need to create the CLI version of unity
stathizzzz: John Lemon is it the guy singing "Imagine all the gameobjects"??
myaocat: 448 views what
anthraxvirus322: sure SeemsGood
veomx: Im from Bavaria thats why im interested
Dimendz: Parameters, now we're talking
NoneFuture: Okay
knilecrack: Bavarishen motor werke
spoco: wysiwyg = cancer
HanksPlay: @georgehotz change the model back to Tpose, maybe is going to offset the arm animation
anthraxvirus322: Just make unity CLI 4Head
Quick_001: WhatTheHeck.. George on a windows machine
anthraxvirus322: its a VM Kappa
myaocat: Is it John Doe?
anthraxvirus322: John Doe monkaS
anthraxvirus322: monkaGiga
Zasuslive: painful to see him waste time with this stuff
Kvann1 : Turn off PlayMod
onu4r: @Zasuslive this is how learning works
stathizzzz: George on Windows is like Game of Thrones season finale 4Head
gofoboso: BrokeBack
Dimendz: It's like vaadin designer but for video games lol
zimxtv: Lol chat needs python and ML
Luki512: Hello @ all
zimxtv: And most importantly chat needs Vim
gofoboso: Yeah py ml
gal40: All nodes in the heirarchy are gameobjects. The outermost John Lemon is a dummy gameobject which encapsulates everything. The inner John Lemon is just the actual model.
Kvann1 : just drag and drop it in obejct
Jeppelelle: drag ub ubti tge cibtrikker fuekd¨
pyythonn: drag it to the right
hintz3y: LMFAO
birrdd: ratirlCoffee
JonThomasK: whats up mr. hotz
Jeppelelle: drag it into the controller field
Staredad: Iirc changes made during playmode is not saved, does this apply to animator controllers too?
Jeppelelle: 👍👍
Luki512: The mic sounds like its stuck into a bread :)
Jeppelelle: This is gonna be a 27 part series :D
Zasuslive: @onu4r I guess if you wanna become an indie developer but he wants to develop an AR platform/product, theres quite a bit of this he can skip (e.g. character animation)
knilecrack: why it's good
myaocat: mic is ok
gal40: You are currently in Play Mode. Changes are not saved when in Play Mode
birrdd: broski
machinelearningbot: what is he drinking>?
JumpTwiice: Kappa sure
SpecialAgentSkye: Mic isnt that bad tbh. Its good for a laptop mic imo
rhytual: Kappa
knilecrack: piss
JonThomasK: liberal tears @machinelearningbot
revolutionist123: Kappa
myaocat: macbook mic is crap
myaocat: also you hear the keys
Bloodspark_: it's okay
mondeverest: drink more coffee to speed things up
Kvann1 : @georgehotz Turn off PlayMod, changes are not saved
trader_f: Show a tour of your million dollar mansion
showzennn: @georgehotz Click JohnLemon Add Component and add a Script than u can use GameObject references and drag the Unity objects to the Script references
spoco: If you could just write code, I would pick up Unity right now, but this stuff is so off putting that I can't even
pentaquant: @georgehotz I bought a new razer blade advanced mer white. Fucking beautiful
knilecrack: he is walking away from you
myaocat: john lennon
gal40: @spoco I use unity and I never ever do this. He is following some tutorial but you can do everything with code
myaocat: ^ i heard
veomx: order a starbucks cold brew venti
Kvann1 : @georgehotz Turn off PlayMod, changes are not saved BlessRNG
Bloodspark_: alive monkaS
gofoboso: maybe you should do that tutorial beforehand
slimyoof: LUL
redbullwiiings: goddamnit john lemon
knilecrack: told ya
Bloodspark_: Fisicks Pepega
stathizzzz: John lemon has left the building...oh wait.. no buildings !! Kappa
Bloodspark_: No gravity
spoco: @gal40 ok good to know
saulgd: click and drag strim ResidentSleeper
Darth_Kirias: wtf that doesn't look like john lenon
trader_f: game designer ResidentSleeper
Bloodspark_: Noob LULW
mybestman: Try rigidbody 2D?
Darth_Kirias: blueprints ResidentSleeper
gal40: You are editing the Prefab. The john lemon in the scene is not connected to the prefab.
pyythonn: increase mass?
SpecialAgentSkye: Should i sub to you for the dopamine rush @georgehotz ? 🤔
myaocat: HYPE LETS GO
slimyoof: monkaS
Dimendz: MonkaW
gofoboso: u
Kvann1 : Need some RigidBody
youngsachi: WutFace
revolutionist123: BibleThump
veomx: :D
c19946: it 's impossible you can write code in this stream
gofoboso: tutorial inception
redbullwiiings: BibleThump hes dead
gofoboso: watching a tutorial inside a tutorial
knilecrack: :D
Bloodspark_: BibleThump byebye
imageliner: @specialagentskye you asked this twice now do it and don't regret it! KomodoHype
c19946: lemon fucked up
discipleyo: yoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
aerotone: its z pos
aerotone: nvm
rstk1: windows machine,
veomx: almost AAA already
veomx: at least alpha
Bloodspark_: yeah hitbox
Lazysloth: john lemon = lemon grab unacceptable
slimyoof: VoHiYo
Bloodspark_: PogCHamp Clap
c19946: why they name this animal john lemon?
revolutionist123: me :)
Bloodspark_: PogChamp Clap
grizvok: how long has he been live?
Kvann1 : You can use JavaScript Kappa
Lazysloth: his head looks like lemon probably
Bloodspark_: C# :/
Hazor90: !uptime
Lazysloth: no u can't use javascript
gofoboso: because it's catchy
gal40: JavaScript is no longer supported.
aiis: He's been live 49 minutes
Lazysloth: it was never supported
gal40: It actually was never supported because it was a javascript clone named UnityScript not javascript itself
grizvok: @aiis thank you
JumpTwiice: outdated visual studios LUL
Zasuslive: Isit cool if I shill my indie game just once 😅
c19946: he said script
Dimendz: C# Pog
Lazysloth: does he have unityvs installed
Yellow_turd: you're so hot when you type like that
leveledgod: @Zasuslive ask forgiveness not permission
PabloBree: white IDE NotLikeThis
Bloodspark_: NotLikeThis
youngsachi: WutFace
knilecrack: ctrl shit home/end to select everything
revolutionist123: my eyes are burning with that white IDE WutFace
Staredad: LUL
asthmaa: vs2019?
Bioaim7: that he even uses an IDE is gigantic
Bloodspark_: D:
knilecrack: change theme
Zasuslive: @leveledgod check it out on yt Project Fox Online. Based on metal gear solid 4’s multiplayer
Harm133: you can set the IDE to dark mode
Zasuslive: Forgive me guyzzz
Lazysloth: install vim extension for VS
Kiddepants: Not gonna lie, first live stream from tomcr00se :D
Hazor90: you can change theme to dark in settings
mehi9h: just make it dark pls
darkwon_: visual studio has dark mode built in
gal40: Tools > Options > Environment > General > Color Theme > Dark
stathizzzz: George there is a Dark Mode in Visual Stdio if it suits you
Bloodspark_: :horn:
smurfd0: .. or just grab gvim
Lazysloth: gvim is meh
twitchistrash788: Csharp is best with VS
Dimendz: People that don't use dark mode in any IDE are psychopaths
aladdin_mck: Use Emacs!
BookRaider: use notepad like a real man
veomx: after comes the yoko ono extension pack
aladdin_mck: Yea fr
elyaizen: your setup look really good man, you need dark mode
Lazysloth: thats for controlleers probably
Zasuslive: A real editor has yellow as its background, easier on the eyes :))
Lazysloth: for joysticks
gal40: Input.GetAxis returns the displacement from the middle of the controller. It works for both joysticks, and wasd/arrows.
KyleUE: did this dude just gatekeep editors?
Bioaim7: duduuumm
BlackSords: how about using unity platform instead?
Lazysloth: does self driving stuff quat is hard tho
myaocat: @gal40 are you israeli?
gal40: Yes
myaocat: ma kore :)
spoco: @Zasuslive with cyan text right? Kappa
liquidcomb: WutFace STOP
avagyannarek: @gal40 Are you illuminati?
grizvok: vscode intellisense is incredible
Lazysloth: gal = wonder women SeemsGood
supremad: jetbrains FTW
Kiddepants: Xcode or Visual Studio?
asthmaa: @grizvok have you tried intellijidea?
keepingtrckofthisacct: @gal40 hi, do you stream?
gal40: No
gofoboso: ReSharper
twitchistrash788: Intellij requires a beastly machine to run smoothly
BookRaider: get off his dick guys give him some space
Acles123: ctrl shift end/home
keepingtrckofthisacct: @gal40 looks like you should :)
Knarez: whats the deal with his new computer
Zasuslive: @spoco cyan is a godly colour :]
CraftyGaming: OnAnimatorMove is a built in function
Lazysloth: new computer = windows gasp
zneel_73: bro your can is empty since at leat half an hour
Bombapil0t: windows, bling bling ide, game dev NotLikeThis
twitchistrash788: T POSE
Bloodspark_: No, 1/2 dab
gal40: The Animator component will automatically look for the OnAnimatorMove and call it
xaxxjs: hi bro
miths: georgehotz stuck in tutorial hell LUL
Knarez: right click task bar -> cortana -> hidden
Knarez: thank me later Kappa
Bloodspark_: LUL
Lethly: what are the specs of the new computer?
Knarez: LUL
Lazysloth: ew
Crypod: LUL
smurfd0: strutting like aboss
Bloodspark_: PogChamp Clap
shinzxc_: PogChamp
grizvok: LOL
revolutionist123: PogChamp
Kvann1 : PogChamp
youngsachi: PogChamp
orochiviia: PogChamp
the_best_russian_bear: PogChamp PogChamp
cIvIcbooks: fuckin jon lemon
stathizzzz: Walking on his toes PogChamp
BookRaider: time to run away kids
JumpTwiice: LUL
gofoboso: they see me rolling
Bloodspark_: no omnidirectional movement LUL
CraftyGaming: Man, for once I know more about something than George
JumpTwiice: gachiBASS ASS ETS
zneel_73: empty can bro
aiis: LUL
Lazysloth: nice headset
Bioaim7: LUL
Zasuslive: ffs g2g. Near the end of the stream if George has a lil break and does somewhat of a Q/A can someone just ask where we sign up to help break the simulation (im srs loll) will watch the stream on yt later
Bloodspark_: LULW
EddieTex: you using windows bro? lol
stathizzzz: Nice sunglasses
Bloodspark_: what
Lethly: what are the specs of the computer?
M03x: am an c# student should i get into unity ? or just switch to java it has more job opportunities 4Head ?
Lazysloth: judge dredd cosplay
Bombapil0t: :D
twitchistrash788: He's drinking redbull
JumpTwiice: LUL true
UniversalGeneve: LUL LUL
revolutionist123: TriHard
Bloodspark_: It's a Razer Laptop, I saw an i7 8th gen and GPU idk
asthmaa: @M03x kotlin
asthmaa: java old
shinzxc_: @Lethly razer blade 15
CraftyGaming: I just got a job in java because it pays more, fuck java
grizvok: or go
Lethly: cheers
elyaizen: have you found a name for your AR machine?
Muratandjose: D:
Knarez: LUL
manutdgeo: @georgehotz dude, you are like an idol to me, been seeing some of your wokr since the ps3 exploits, keep it up man !!!
Zasuslive: lmaoo
borkloverr2: What do you think about swift?
BookRaider: Java died in 2007 when oracle bought Sun
twitchistrash788: lmao
trader_f: sardBan sardBan sardBan
Bloodspark_: monkaS
Maakishoot: where can I find this unity tutorial?
stathizzzz: Im a JAVA hater too SeemsGood SeemsGood SeemsGood SeemsGood SeemsGood
M03x: LUL
Bloodspark_: BAN monkaS
tigopotter: george why did you quit comma.ai??
shinzxc_: JAVA (puke)
miths: Java is love, Java is life <3
Dimendz: Why do java devs need glasses? Because they can't C# PepeLaugh
Zasuslive: me
Harm133: me me
Muratandjose: are python questions banned here aswell
M03x: @asthmaa is kootlin based on java ?
CraftyGaming: Mod me
JumpTwiice: me PogChamp
grizvok: @Dimendz LOL
elyaizen: me
nanodanger7: me
discipleyo: me
Bioaim7: TypeScript <3
Zasuslive: oh nvm subs only
Lethly: i have subscribed for a long time
miths: MEME
Knarez: me Kappa
youngsachi: TriHard
Muratandjose: no me :)
trader_f: not me
Bloodspark_: me :) pls
Lazysloth: lol don't even want the power
nanodanger7: one year man :D
asthmaa: @M03x yes
avagyannarek: JAVA is PHP
hintz3y: cheer1 me
the_best_russian_bear: me Kappa
tanoshiizo: that guy
gl3nn_wolf3: I'll do it
shinzxc_: 12 mo PogChamp
Maakishoot: JAVA suck Python for life
Bloodspark_: fuck
Erciks: i dont. Mod means responsiblty
Rellekz: me
Kiddepants: This is my first live stream lmao.
khronicz: khronicz subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months!
Knarez: LOL dude the blue crown is not a sub
Kiddepants: On here
stathizzzz: Who s in the mob??? PogChamp
JumpTwiice: not even a sub LUL
Knarez: it's only twitch prime
zneel_73: LUL
MatiGoG: monkaS
imageliner: LUL
Knarez: LUL
trader_f: sard17
Bombapil0t: mod @nanodanger7 :D
slimyoof: LUL
Knarez: no
khronicz: khronicz subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months!
orochiviia: froggenPega
aerotone: LUL no
Zasuslive: xD
Knarez: only if they subscribe with it haha
gal40: If you are seriously interested in using windows, you might want to look into WSL (ubuntu in windows)
grizvok: you get the same from twitch prime
zneel_73: scams
Muratandjose: he doesnt know LUL
CraftyGaming: shhh nerds relax
M03x: @asthmaa is it only for mobile ?
discipleyo: if I sub can I get mod?
nanodanger7: im here
UniversalGeneve: LUL
eyep1e: just mod everyone
Knarez: LUL
th3_maj0r: a lot of subscribes now ahaha
mondeverest: bogaShh bogaShh bogaShh
trader_f: he wil ban all LUL
M03x: scammed LUL
JumpTwiice: monkaS incel mods
kaanfsd0: love making money is meh :(((
hintz3y: kappa1 I'm the top cheerer
meeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeenz: hey. what are we doing today?
twitchistrash788: Elevate me
Erciks: LuL
Dimendz: Go for partner ship
the_best_russian_bear: desertukMoncat
stathizzzz: Mod me for non subsrcibers PogChamp
o_sagga: me toooo
nanodanger7: yay
asthmaa: @M03x no, they working for native, ios, android, web server all
zneel_73: LUL
Bioaim7: aren't you sell out now ? @georgehotz LUL
Howi_: LUL
javadragoniv: @georgehotz i can only guess with a name like mine i can sub for eternity and i wouldnt get mod huh
Luki512: Where you see the follow date?
grizvok: he's a shifting fucker
revolutionist123: This chat this some more emotes
grizvok: shifty*
Scheback: how long will be the stream ?
M03x: @asthmaa thank you SeemsGood
eyep1e: VR sims coding
JumpTwiice: WutFace
grizvok: MY EARS
shinzxc_: WutFace
twitchistrash788: WHoa
Bioaim7: aren't you sell out now ? @georgehotz
Zasuslive: woahwoah
myaocat: yes
MatiGoG: WutFace
Muratandjose: WutFace
Erciks: yep
sDeRs122: yes
zneel_73: monkaS
tanoshiizo: WutFace
eyep1e: REKT
youngsachi: WutFace
aerotone: WutFace
Bombapil0t: CurseLit
Yellow_turd: WutFace
grizvok: FUCK MY EARS ARE BLEEDING
Staredad: WutFace
trader_f: owh shit
revolutionist123: This chat needs some more emotes**
nanodanger7: lol
Xavur_: monkaS
discipleyo: NotLikeThis
Dimendz: WutFace
Kiddepants: That's loud lol
UniversalGeneve: haha
Lazysloth: fireplace is loud
Kvann1 : WutFace
javadragoniv: fuck yeah
stathizzzz: I cant hear nothing, Im deaf Kappa
Bloodspark_: Bloodspark_ subscribed at Tier 1.
Zasuslive: its called ambience and its killing many speakers and headphones rn
grizvok: my earssssssss
imageliner: LUL
Yellow_turd: still there WutFace
Rlchibi: stop play
slimyoof: NotLikeThis
JumpTwiice: WutFace WINDOWS SOUNDS
M03x: WutFace
sDeRs122: omg that kinda painfull
jedynka_trygonometryczna: @georgehotz is it you bmw on instagram?
youngsachi: WutFace WutFace
the_best_russian_bear: sova96RipEars sova96RipEars
avagyannarek: same
slimyoof: i hear static
gofoboso: it's windy
shinzxc_: LOUDER FeelsGoodMan Clap
Bloodspark_: WutFace PLS
M03x: windows WutFace
mehi9h: oh thank god
Xavur_: why no linux :(
revolutionist123: WutFace
grizvok: my headphones were kinda loud
grizvok: jesus
Bloodspark_: mod me :)
UniversalGeneve: sound card broken?
Kvann1 : @georgehotz Turn off PlayMod, changes are not saved BlessRNG
Lazysloth: play mode isn't saved
Rlchibi: yeah any changes made in play mode doesnt stick
CraftyGaming: The only changes that will save in play mode are prefab modifications like materials and such
gofoboso: kookoobird
miths: What kind of game are you going to build? georgehotz
JumpTwiice: wasd to move cam around
Enriquetecfan: Why are you learing unity ¿?
gofoboso: this one 1-0
Bombapil0t: squeeze some $ @Enriquetecfan
Bloodspark_: So close to cam monkaS
meeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeenz: jhon lemon = john lennon?
Staredad: @Enriquetecfan AR
Kvann1 : Double click on game object, to zoom it
IWasnotDemi: @georgehotz I love you
Bloodspark_: John Lemon: The Adventure :)
JumpTwiice: the keys W, A, S, D to move editor cam
JumpTwiice: NotLikeThis
Enriquetecfan: Thanks Chat !
CraftyGaming: With the Directional light selected, you can press 'e' to change to the rotation widget
dorkmo: vladimir lenin?
CraftyGaming: r, to scale, and W for transform
miths: y u no create own game engine? PepeHands
zneel_73: freezes
smurfd0: think ur dropping frames...
Lazysloth: fps = 11 lul
flitnlockphilly: Dude just make your own game engine in visual basic, like bisquit would
Bloodspark_: @miths LUL funny
M03x: @georgehotz can you get rich with unity ? 4Head
UniversalGeneve: @georgehotz do you have a stream schedule, or just whenever you have time?
stathizzzz: Bisqwit god !
flitnlockphilly: don't worry, it is
JumpTwiice: u bet LUL
CraftyGaming: It's pretty hard to watch tbh
miths: I don't know unity but it is still painful
M03x: @stathizzzz 1 SeemsGood
HanksPlay: trihard1 trihard1 trihard1 trihard1 trihard1
flitnlockphilly: Hackerman spends 12 hours learning how to use basic UI
Bloodspark_: ol
M03x: LUL
JumpTwiice: imagine using vim LUL
gofoboso: 666
birrdd: ratirlCoffee interesting
gofoboso: 999
CraftyGaming: nav mesh is the real magic
kevczy: Vim for unity? That sounds disgusting
Bloodspark_: true :D
gofoboso: 333
M03x: @birrdd ratiirlTip
M03x: nvm FeelsBadMan
birrdd: @M03x ratirlTip
my_curiosity: @georgehotz is this project related to the car ai thing or are you doing something other for fun ?
adriaroms: new computer?
birrdd: ratirl subs in here, LUL
M03x: @birrdd while he is live LUL
kevczy: @adriaroms yea
Zasuslive: 160p exists wtf lol least I can stream the audio
birrdd: amazing!
Bloodspark_: LUL
adriaroms: @kevczy specs?
birrdd: @Risky2001 so bored?
gal40: NavMesh is the mesh of where an ai agent can walk.
kevczy: @adriaroms umm it was in the beginning of the vid
birrdd: is there a command for ur new pc specs?
miths: What are the specs on your new pc?
Zasuslive: gal40 indie dev?
mikeyyinspace: !specs
adriaroms: !motherfuckerSpecs
Bloodspark_: !specs Kappa
CraftyGaming: Ctrl s is muscle memory for me now, along with ctrl shift s in visual studio
Yellow_turd: What are the specs on your new pc?
HanksPlay: i dont think is boring
gal40: On my free time
Lazysloth: Intel Pentium Processor
HanksPlay: crash
kevczy: The stream looks pretty decent
birrdd: pentium PogChamp
Bloodspark_: Thhis is pretty entertaining for me at least
JumpTwiice: PogChamp
adriaroms: !newMonsterPCspecs
Bloodspark_: PogChamp BEAST
JumpTwiice: monkaS deth
my_curiosity: i thought he was a mac guy :D
youngsachi: PogChamp
UniversalGeneve: bigARms
mikeyyinspace: i heard soda improves blood circulation Kappa
M03x: can i use unity on my i5 820m geforce ?? DeelsBadMan
flitnlockphilly: What would you do if george hots slapped your girlfriends ass
gofoboso: Al
Xavur_: slap his ass
kevczy: @flitnlockphilly I’ll Give it to him
gofoboso: all the muscle is in the fingers
Bloodspark_: @M03x barely maybe but the more complex your project becomes the more it's gonna lag and shit
Lazysloth: probably some rich people water in a can
kevczy: What is that drink?
Bloodspark_: LUL
flitnlockphilly: Can I run this project on my voodoo 2?
Bombapil0t: DansGame
Bloodspark_: HAHAHA
HanksPlay: eco? why not google home?
stathizzzz: Bad boy
tigopotter: george why did you left comma.ai?
kevczy: Why are you going doo doo
UniversalGeneve: *NY accent* computer~
Bloodspark_: WHAT
FartKnockGomez: this is how skynet starts DansGame
CraftyGaming: I think I'll name my next dog Alexa, just to create a little chaos
UniversalGeneve: LUL
Muratandjose: i thought i heard my name
hawkield: Windows? DansGame
gofoboso: lol
Caene: Justin who? Kappa
UniversalGeneve: WutFace
mondeverest: bogaS
stathizzzz: Justin who??? WutFace
FartKnockGomez: LUL what a douche
UniversalGeneve: justice beaver
CraftyGaming: You will use multiple cameras in most solutions
kevczy: Ok now it’s about comedian
gofoboso: blieber
jotembruv: how come u didnt go with ue4
JumpTwiice: this tutorial is scuffed af LUL
stathizzzz: Only justing I knew was justin.tv
KrakkenTM: Hellooooo @georgehotz
adriaroms: specs?
W1lkins: Was the refactor of minikeyvalue from python to Go streamed?
Kheri0n: will you be creating ai world in unity?
KrakkenTM: still not verified here? LUL
knilecrack: you should've named him GeorgeLemon
Caene: monkaS
gofoboso: DrinkPurple
stathizzzz: Change this house to a rock Opera hall and let john give a concert PogChamp
kevczy: What is the drink)))))))?
gofoboso: BCWarrior SwiftRage PJSalt
KrakkenTM: F?
Caene: F
Muratandjose: f
youngsachi: f
zbszx: LONG LIVE THE STREAM
mondeverest: bogaBusted bogaBusted bogaBusted
foxubu: foxubu subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 8 months, currently on a 1 month streak!
mondeverest: bogaQ
Bloodspark_: F
salihyil1: why u learn unity?
gofoboso: long live rock n roll
Lazysloth: refresh plebs
Bloodspark_: no :)
CraftyGaming: You dropped frames, they are paying respect. F in unity will focus on the selected object
el_pirulote: it's the f word
Kheri0n: PogChamp
gofoboso: rainbow
PhosphoricAcid: F
KrakkenTM: f
Caene: Would be fun to see you progress from noob to not-so-much-noob over streams. Could be fun.
mondeverest: keeps freezing for me
zneel_73: F
zbszx: alright guys, does anyone know neural networks built with pytorch? i am struggling w/ my homework
stathizzzz: 0.5 Fps
knilecrack: yeah
gofoboso: lag
the_best_russian_bear: F karmik4
foxubu: freezing
Darkhunder1: f
CraftyGaming: Full F
kevczy: Focus
markovchain21: unity ate him alive
KrakkenTM: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YOBM5UaeTXk
markovchain21: razer pogg
mondeverest: bogaGood
HanksPlay: i want to see @georgehotz playing VR Chat!
Rlchibi: are you still streaming to Taiwan xDD
kevczy: I’m good
Lazysloth: saved!
Bloodspark_: LUL
Darkhunder1: ok
markovchain21: @KrakkenTM ellinas ?
Caene: It said Taiwan there though LUL
Caene: Legit
foxubu: 0 kb/s :o
KrakkenTM: @markovchain21 yy
naix_1337: PogChamp live again
buhrmi4tw: aaayyy
Bloodspark_: oh back
foxubu: pppkay
Xavur_: omg thats bad
Caene: The pixels LUL
kevczy: Hm unity never helps my lige
KarlaVxleria: : (
foxubu: blurry :(
kevczy: Life*
stathizzzz: 75 Mbps download, 3 Mbps upload LUL
Bloodspark_: potato stream HYPERS
Caene: It's better than nothing!
Xavur_: have you tried turning router off and on again? LUL
Caene: LOL
kevczy: There it’s back
Nougekai: @georgehotz what do you think learning machine learning (python) as a neurosurgeon? Worth the try, or is it too much?
salihyil1: 160p
spoco: welcome back to 2005 Kappa
Bloodspark_: oh saved again lol
foxubu: Someone is jamming your wifi ^_^
THX1342: Привет гопник
Bloodspark_: quality is fine again PogChamp
knilecrack: okay
Caene: Smooth fps now though
kevczy: Dude I bet Starbucks WiFi will work better then this
stathizzzz: Are you on 56k modem? PogChamp
Bloodspark_: except fps
Caene: Check for shady vans outside
Fantasma56: F
zneel_73: you fucked up showing your ip
markovchain21: sony devs are payback time :D
NoLimitFitness: are you connected to teheran again?
THX1342: гопник стрем
Dsplits: @georgehotz you look alot skinnier
mikeyyinspace: get off the phone itll speed up ur internet Kappa
UniversalGeneve: LUL
kodApan: RIP
jotembruv: NotLikeThis
knilecrack: hi agagin
CraftyGaming: Here we go boys
joiput: LUL
naix_1337: 1 Megabit? PunchTrees
Caene: Is this NA internet?
knilecrack: 0
CraftyGaming: squint your eyes and maybe you'll be able to read some of the larger text
mikeyyinspace: PunchTrees
mondeverest: bogaHacker
SpecialAgentSkye: Close Limewire. Sometimes takes a lot of bandwidth Kappa
kodApan: saved
mikeyyinspace: F
CraftyGaming: Actually looks good
markovchain21: F
Chris_XIX: F
Bloodspark_: cant read SeesmGood
Chris_XIX: Lost it again
Bloodspark_: SeemsGood
knilecrack: it' good
markovchain21: good now
mondeverest: bogaGood
spoco: works now
kevczy: Yea
THX1342: cheeki breeki cat
Rlchibi: probably the server you are on
Xavur_: zeeman internet
icanthitthose: what's happening
THX1342: just code an 8bit game
CraftyGaming: refresh if your screen is black
Bloodspark_: it's shitty nevertheless LUL
knilecrack: you can focus search bar with alt d
THX1342: make a roguelike
kevczy: Recommend youtube
Caene: Use your phone for internet. LUL
THX1342: there~s no graphics
knilecrack: it's good now
Caene: Phone hotspot LUL
SpecialAgentSkye: Its fine. Its not bad at all
Dsplits: moving into the game dev industry now?
markovchain21: it is like 100% fine now !!
Harm133: can jailbreak the first iphone but cant properly stream LUL
knilecrack: tes
knilecrack: it's good mann
markovchain21: you need jailbreak..
Xavur_: call your provider and complain
CraftyGaming: Since you went to 1Mb it looks fine man
SpecialAgentSkye: Can break Sony security but cant get good internet LUL
THX1342: it~s good
kevczy: Dude just go to McDonald’s
Bloodspark_: not 100% but okay LUL
Caene: @markovchain21 You will eat those words, just saying.
th3_maj0r: Faq windows
JumpTwiice: 4Head just get a house
kevczy: McDonald’s WiFi looks like to work better
markovchain21: @Caene ?
CraftyGaming: Señor lemon
Caene: @markovchain21 You will see
Lazysloth: u made that headset brah
Bloodspark_: PogChamp John Lemon AR
markovchain21: @Caene not even humor or jokes allowed?
KrakkenTM: @markovchain21 na fantastw spoudazeis/spoudases kati panw se upologistes?
Nougekai: @georgehotz what do you think learning machine learning (python) as a brain surgeon? Worth the try, or is it too much and better make a friend who knows ML/DP?
Bloodspark_: Chat is annoying :)
knilecrack: twitch chat most toxic ever
Bloodspark_: ban them :)
meshuggahsahin: o hey KonCha
THX1342: "work" hobbT
JumpTwiice: @knilecrack chats like this one are the least toxic ones compared to big streamers' chat
knilecrack: it's awesome now
Bloodspark_: It's working now
prakyath_kantharaju: learning is always is good.. But if you are looking for a friend
icanthitthose: what kind of game is he building
fuuqtv: true
KrakkenTM: @georgehotz hows comma.ai going?
fuuqtv: if i have bad internet i dont like the place
Xavur_: 5G is coming soon lol
Caene: I think @markovchain21 is right, it seems stable now. SeemsGood
knilecrack: @JumpTwiice that's what I thought, twitch chat in genral. This is fine
Xavur_: 5G will be good for streaming
eyep1e: building simsAI?
markovchain21: @Caene i am sorry, if i offended you. i am new to this stream
Caene: Huh? I love you
Caene: @markovchain21 <3
stathizzzz: The CIA is watching out for you and reroutes all your traffic to thir servers, hence the bad internet PogChamp
fkndean: BOOOOOOOOOOO
fkndean: hi
Xavur_: unity looks so outdated :/
knilecrack: yeah
THX1342: @georgehotz have you heard of Godot? Open source competitor to unity
gal40: Why are you dealing with post-processing so early on?
Lazysloth: if cia is watching order some pizza
tigopotter: which one is your new computer?
foxubu: So much clicking to get things work ...
meatballsimproved: what's the game going to be about?
Bloodspark_: Raytracing PogChamp
CraftyGaming: See, this tutorial is telling you how to make a scene look great but isnt teaching you major design concepts
KyleUE: i need raytracing on my AR girlfriend.
Bloodspark_: same :)
foxubu: @CraftyGaming true words
Poethick: @KyleUE LUL
markovchain21: maybe it will get better at the end again
gal40: I don't get why you are messing with post processing when you don't have much of a game yet
Bloodspark_: He's following this tutorial :)
Lazysloth: it is because he is on the camera section
osaidaz99: is this going to be uploaded on youtube?
Dsplits: you should make a game from scratch in C
Bloodspark_: PogChamp
Lazysloth: what can go wrong lol
CraftyGaming: get into using delegates and events, coroutines and fun coding stuff
UniversalGeneve: he's going off the grid!
foxubu: @osaidaz99 Search for Comma ai archive. Disclaimer: not his channel.
Lazysloth: autopilot off
asaalgk: you should check out unity machine learning agents toolkit, its fun and easy
Dsplits: btw can't believe that you're on windows
Lazysloth: YOU MADE IT!
knilecrack: why everyone hates windows
JumpTwiice: background makes it seem like you're streaming from heaven
CraftyGaming: Guarantee someone followed this tutorial and it is a game on the google play store Kappa
Zipzipcekirge: fun fact you can enable unity dark mode by changing a branch instruction
Kheri0n: do you have any degree?
bunnydd: use godot engine
CraftyGaming: I frequent r/gamedev and r/unity3d. So many people post their store pages for tutorial games
dMunkei: @Zipzipcekirge what you mean?
dragan2271: hi bro
dragan2271: whats computer specifications
Zipzipcekirge: get a debugger and search for skin symbol. There is a jmp eq instruction if you make it jump not equal it will get into dark mode @dMunkei
Rojaster: he is doing game right now?
dMunkei: @Zipzipcekirge What do you mean by get a debugger?
JumpTwiice: @Rojaster he's just tryna learn unity
Lazysloth: you can just change the hex in the unity editor and it will be dark mode
Rojaster: @JumpTwiice for fun ?
JumpTwiice: @Rojaster possibly for future projects?
CraftyGaming: There is a unity plugin for VS that will allow you to attach it to the unity process for debugging, its fantastic
Chris_XIX: @dragan2271 8th gen i7, 32gb of ram
Nesquik80: @georgehotz you like mac or windows more?
ayman_saleh: Why windows and not linux?
asaalgk: lmao
Panda1Express: LUL
UniversalGeneve: good friend
gal40: When in 2d mode you have to seriously scroll out, because the canvas is huge
Bloodspark_: LUL PogChamp
CraftyGaming: "she" PogChamp
Xavur_: do another speedtest then :)
funwayz: she PogU
lukaakul005: ur crazy
knilecrack: what means pogu
knilecrack: twitch ebonics
fkndean: if you only knew the way
fkndean: of twitch ebonics
mikeyyinspace: why ebonics
mikeyyinspace: twitch isnt black cmonBruh
JumpTwiice: cuz TriHard
Xavur_: CruW
knilecrack: cuz
Bloodspark_: cmonBruh
Dsplits: no it's like that visual studio forces that name convention
mikeyyinspace: he must not know what ebonics means
mikeyyinspace: itd be twitch lingo
youngsachi: TriHard
knilecrack: it's ebonics black ppl lingo?
stathizzzz: Unity's procedural coding style is not your style, you're more generic guy
CraftyGaming: abstraction!
gal40: You accidentally put two instances of the script
CraftyGaming: public variables can be set in the editor, or those marked with [SerializeField]
estilen: 500k in my account by next year
JumpTwiice: @georgehotz favorite language? dont say python
erenesmer: !keyboard
smurfd0: he kinda looks liek Rick from rock and morty ;)
knilecrack: where is sprint?
julien9877: todo: sprinting
julien9877: LUL
CraftyGaming: literally just change one float, LUL
Artbarte: sup
knilecrack: gg
erenesmer: !keyboard
CraftyGaming: You said you wanted to move faster
Darkhunder1: camera
julien9877: no change 1 float to increase walking speed
knilecrack: it's good don't bother man
Bloodspark_: LUL
gal40: Application.quit is ignored while in the editor
RRHDS: going to make a game?
showzennn: is at the end
LoLskiller1: what tutorial do you follow?
JumpTwiice: no
mikeyyinspace: fine for me
knilecrack: no
aathove: no
knilecrack: don't touch
Darkhunder1: no
liquidcomb: fine
nanodanger7: no
UniversalGeneve: it's good
youngsachi: maybe
nestradalink2: good for me
Quidos: VoteNay
aathove: you dude <3
julien9877: do it xqcM
JumpTwiice: PagChomp pvc viewers
julien9877: xqcN ?
showzennn: change turn speed
JumpTwiice: being a pleb FeelsGoodMan
nestradalink2: kfc emotes are the best
knilecrack: if you need g's IP you have it
alluxua: sing a song, please, geohot
tigopotter: which one is your computer?
gal40: After you normalize the movement vector you can set its magnitude
julien9877: put it to 500 PogChamp
JumpTwiice: Input.GetAxis() is between -1 and 1
Vjasal: hello @georgehotz
knilecrack: wooooooooo
julien9877: xqcFast
bubabii: omegaLuL
CraftyGaming: Hacker PogChamp
showzennn: ahahha
showzennn: LUL
andrex_andrex: ehehe
cIvIcbooks: fuckin jon lemon
Bloodspark_: Speedrun hacks
zneel_73: LUL
julien9877: new sonic trailer PogChamp
jacopo_l98: xqcFast
tigopotter: which one is your computer?
knilecrack: gigasonic razor
Lokimjolnir: hello everyone
th3_maj0r: Razer 15 lsxyzOk
jagger_rsw: whoa... george is programming in spreadsheets or sth :)
grizvok: ROFL
gal40: When you edit inspector variables while in play mode they are not saved
Darkhunder1: camera
ArcherCreatlol: hey geohot, ur qira docker file doesnt work, could u update it?
mikeyyinspace: !uptime
Darkhunder1: change camera in stream
JumpTwiice: 4Head
noodlearms_1: hey
ShinzoLK: Did you leave comma ai? If so, why?
gal40: Well I g2g. Have fun learning unity
ArcherCreatlol: what's ur goal in learning unity?
data_day_life: data_day_life gifted a Tier 1 sub to gal40! This is their first Gift Sub in the channel!
Dqyijote: Well I g2g. Have fun learning unity
littlezippy92: I think unreal is easier to learn to use
th3_maj0r: ahahah
codevisionary: have you considered building your own game engine @georgehotz ?
local_root: whaaaaaaaaaaaat? geohot and windows?????
fkndean: first time i seen george on a windows
BIakerTv: why the m_name syntax?
fkndean: KappaRoss
knilecrack: 1st time george seen georgd on windows
local_root: m_ = member variable
th3_maj0r: lol
JumpTwiice: python syntax LUL
fkndean: syntax game
BIakerTv: gotcha thanks
fkndean: If you wanna write good code write it in HolyC Kappa
local_root: @fkndean on templeos of course too
fkndean: oh yeah bby
fkndean: I would pay to see George try that lmfao
caslecasle: caslecasle subscribed with Twitch Prime.
julien9877: xqcPrime
BIakerTv: little hint i learned in college - if you type it all out yourself, it's not plagiarism ;) (jk)
local_root: what's the sudden change or the reason why he's programming a game??
knilecrack: because of AR
alluxua: geohot is always random. No reason
dorkmo: AR
knilecrack: he is making some AR set with big field of view
caslecasle: Am i subscribed
local_root: interesting
dotEXEguy: out causes arguments to be passed by reference
knilecrack: dude wants to be better on every field
smurfd0: https://www.c-sharpcorner.com/article/out-variables-in-c-sharp-7-0/
caslecasle: -
local_root: im just glad it's not java
alluxua: probably he always has passion on tuning hardware
littlezippy92: @local_root geohot is getting into pirating games and making cracks
local_root: @littlezippy92 definitely!
littlezippy92: KappaClaus
julien9877: just use || DansGame
Knarez: that tutorial isn't consistent about its spaces between the if and condition parenthesis REEEEE
codevisionary: every real programmer's goal is to do everything you can possibly do with a computer, and one of those things is developing games
local_root: @Knarez probably because the person who made the tutorial used tabs instead of spaces smh
caslecasle: Mod me ploxerino
codevisionary: tabs > spaces
Knarez: nah it looked like they just forgot it it one of the snippets lol
local_root: tabs that convert into spaces >>>>>
Wansie: why are you doing this?
sharpblade95: cheer1000
th3_maj0r: Probably asking for mod is the worst way to get it
caslecasle: Nah not with him
dorkmo: heyguys1
caslecasle: seen it happen
ef_0ne: because why the fuck not
ef_0ne: stop asking
th3_maj0r: lol
pandatastisch9: what's happening here?
gznn: he having fun whats the problam
codevisionary: things are happening
poopboy7: tabs are overrated smh
codevisionary: nope
codevisionary: tabs are superior
cosmoz_AI: why unity ?
godlessmonkey: Is this your first time with Unity?
codevisionary: @georgehotz build your own game engine and go head to head with Unity
th3_maj0r: Richard in Silicon Valley use tabs and he is a great programmer. Need any other proof?
ef_0ne: PogChamp
sharpblade95: cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1
Caene: PogChamp
Dqyijote: lol
dorkmo: heyguys1
MonsterMannen_: HeyGuys
CraftyGaming: My IDE knows when I press tab, to enter 4 spaces
mikeyyinspace: heyguys1
data_day_life: this is why I hated unity
Lazysloth: change ur camera settings
Lazysloth: its not revealing other stuff
mikeyyinspace: heyguys1
ef_0ne: why not ue4?
dorkmo: heyguys1
mikeyyinspace: heyguys1
showzennn: project -> SampleScene?
dorkmo: heyguys1
mikeyyinspace: heyguys1
local_root: what computer did he get?
dorkmo: heyguys1
Bloodspark_: bruh
mikeyyinspace: heyguys1
CAPTN_136: heyguys1
CraftyGaming: double click on anything in your scene
dorkmo: heyguys1
mikeyyinspace: heyguys1
data_day_life: bad bot
dorkmo: heyguys1
mikeyyinspace: heyguys1
boy_milk: george gimme ur cummies
CraftyGaming: middle click and hold with move the scene around while right click and hold will rotatte your view
data_day_life: quality chat
mikeyyinspace: heyguys1
dorkmo: heyguys1
Bloodspark_: HeyGUys 1 Kappa
Bloodspark_: fuuu
Bloodspark_: HeyGuys 1 kappa
mikeyyinspace: heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1
JumpTwiice: Kappa = GreyFace
smurfd0: u have an error in the bottom of the screen...
mikeyyinspace: heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1 heyguys1
pandatastisch9: my ubuntu image stops at booting wtf
knilecrack: asell out
Bloodspark_: 1 bit LUL
julien9877: my chat experience BibleThump
mikeyyinspace: LUL
pandatastisch9: started user manager for uid 121
zneel_73: sellout
local_root: what computer did you get @georgehotz ?
youngsachi: LUL
pandatastisch9: what does that even mean
codevisionary: where's the morality @georgehotz ?
th3_maj0r: lsxyzLS lsxyzLS lsxyzLS lsxyzLS
JumpTwiice: sellout LUL
knilecrack: bitcoin out
CraftyGaming: You can visualize your raycasts through Debug.DrawLine
cankoloz: LUL
Kadyen: why Unity?
Risx: what're you drinking?
Bloodspark_: why not?
smurfd0: UnassignedReference something something error..
Rojaster: we love money too man, give us money cuz we're watching you
aiis: Is this running on a Tesla computer?
Bloodspark_: @aiis yes Kappa
aiis: LUL
codevisionary: no, only linux runs on tesla computer
Rojaster: Oh, I got it, that's why he is on windows.
CoffeeD2: he's like a supervillain "this new invent will get me all the moneys"
Bloodspark_: exactly :)
local_root: it's so weird seeing him coding in an ide instead of vim
codevisionary: removing tesla hardware just to install windows on it would be a disgrace to humanity
JumpTwiice: D:
nestradalink2: VSC > VS change my mind
mikeyyinspace: PogChamp winner stream
smurfd0: game over man
Caene: monkaS
Caene: I got caught monkaS
codevisionary: atom > vsc
CraftyGaming: obby working code Kreygasm
cosmoz_AI: why unity ?
bubabii: i dont understand what is the reason bug?
knilecrack: text editor wars begin
pentaquant: @georgehotz penis
local_root: notepad.exe >>>
ef_0ne: real programmers use pen and paper
ef_0ne: scrubz
codevisionary: why does that create a link?
Caene: pen and paper A4 scanner >>
Giammanaco: Why he has bought a Windows Computer?
knilecrack: cause it's cheap
knilecrack: with 32gb of ram
local_root: @knilecrack what kind of computer did he get?
CraftyGaming: Unity has a great editor language used to streamline certain repeated actions. Just another layer to learn
knilecrack: razor something
local_root: razer blade?
knilecrack: razer* yeah
pentaquant: Yes
local_root: nice
pentaquant: I just got one and fucking love it
local_root: @pentaquant enjoy it :]
codevisionary: step one: buy razer laptop, step two: overwrite windows with all zeroes, step there: install linux
codevisionary: step four: be a good person
Sydowh: Hello
CraftyGaming: Hello @Sydowh
pentaquant: Well, I've partitioned for linux
pentaquant: but fuck a wipe of windows for linux. I still need to play roblox
ef_0ne: just use proton
codevisionary: cringe
CraftyGaming: Quaternions inc
Sydowh: Good to see you are still learning Kappa
non_pc_character: Heyo! first time watching George
non_pc_character: whats cracking
th3_maj0r: ctrl c ctrl v programming
codevisionary: isn't that what people go to college for? @th3_maj0r
MichaelMcMillan: windows, come on bro?
th3_maj0r: @codevisionary exactly
dragan2271: hi
xxtakki: is there any particular reason why you are learning unity ?
th3_maj0r: He wants to build an AR
local_root: @xxtakki im guessing because of the popularity
codevisionary: @xxtakki
codevisionary: https://clips.twitch.tv/AbrasiveBashfulGrouseNononoCat
codevisionary: this is why
xxtakki: tyy
Pryetranka: george hotz x reason, choose one
dragan2271: @
NonTrivial778: I try to learn unity and I got bored
Kheri0n: @xxtakki i think he wants to become god by creating his ai world in unity
dragan2271: @knilevcrack
CraftyGaming: You know George, I've been hearing a lot of good things about Unity in Linux with these new 2019 builds. Anyone here know more about it?
local_root: @NonTrivial778 probably because the engine does too much for you
Smokinate: george how often are you in san jose bro im from san jo @georgehotz
NonTrivial778: LUL
pandatastisch9: can u program on dmt next time
ibimsmarry: What are your intentions behind learning unity?
NonTrivial778: @georgehotz you made a raw bitcoin transaction
Lazysloth: he has ar headset
CraftyGaming: I do tasks like these in batches between coding
NonTrivial778: yeah
non_pc_character: If george reads this message we are living in a confirmed simulation Kappa
CraftyGaming: click the topmost waypoint, hold shift, then click the bottommost one
Smokinate: so who is george talking to if he never reads chat
vickson12: WHAT IS HE DOING?
Nevermorewinz: @georgehotz is commai still alive?
CraftyGaming: You can change each axis independantly with multiple selection
stathizzzz: Raw bitcoin transaction > game dev, PS jailbreak >>> game dev
non_pc_character: @codevisionary monkaS
metalneck69: Unity DansGame
CraftyGaming: You plebs don't see the potential Unity has in the AR/VR field. John Lemon doesn't mean shit, he is a tool for learning more advanced systems
stathizzzz: I think geo wants to make a Unity world to simulate autonomous car driving with insane ML algos PogChamp
Lazysloth: nope
CraftyGaming: Link your github @codevisionary
th3_maj0r: o
Lazysloth: get rekt
stathizzzz: RE KT
Caene: ^
th3_maj0r: aggressive twitchchat
pandatastisch9: toxic
Lazysloth: unreal engine is ugly, c is painful
metalneck69: “Link ur github” monkaS
th3_maj0r: quite yeah lol
non_pc_character: no sound? DansGame
vtmr: LUL
funwayz: WOW
sharpblade95: you're not getting hired with no sound
Caene: Sounds is overrated anyway 🔇
nestradalink2: the game for deaf people
Kheri0n: make a sounds with your mouth LUL
pandatastisch9: that's the job of the sound programer
Lazysloth: he turned it off because the fireplace was loud
finessin95: I play an mmorpg from 1997, doesn't have sound and it still has an active player base
dorkmo: hot take: soundtracks underrated
stathizzzz: John Lemon is deaf, hence the deaf game
KeyboardOreos: why Unity WutFace
KeyboardOreos: I'm a 3D Artist Kappa
vickson12: @finessin95 Are you talking about old school runescape?
KeyboardOreos: Unity is nice
Caene: @finessin95 Tibia LUL
matt4kr: dude you should check out Unity ML-Agents, it is crazy shit
dorkmo: heyguys1
finessin95: @vickson12 No, what Caene said, Runescape came in like 2002 or something
KeyboardOreos: That room is so bright! Holy shit
Caene: Tibia, super nostalgic stuff. :)
non_pc_character: Pog
Rlchibi: we a twitch gamer now??
ArcherCreatlol: POGGERS
osaidaz99: big fan from saudi arabia :))
JumpTwiice: ANELE ?
osaidaz99: ?
stathizzzz: John Lemon for President monkaS
finessin95: @Caene Probably the game I've had the most fun in
th3_maj0r: wow you should change the topic from Basic Programming to Hardcore gaming
Caene: @finessin95 Yeah, good memories
JumpTwiice: D 💿 C
non_pc_character: Can we preorder this?
CraftyGaming: Casual playthrough
th3_maj0r: Progamer
non_pc_character: 60 dollars and DLC included?
Lazysloth: one eye ghosts
GeorgeHopkins: cheer1 cheer1
mikeyyinspace: ill take this and the season pass
Lazysloth: that ghost is camping
darkwon_: needs sound
KeyboardOreos: PogChamp
finessin95: We found a bug boys
CraftyGaming: Need to up that turn speed in navmesh agents
Caene: John Lemons looks so depressed FeelsBadMan
Muratandjose: is there a point where his eyebrows arent just sad?
slimyoof: stealth god
th3_maj0r: Anyway this is better than Fortine
stathizzzz: JOhn Lemon has shited his pants, thats why he walks that way PogChamp
Lazysloth: lol ghost stuck
smurfd0: ruh roh, u got ghosted :D
th3_maj0r: Fortnite*
routerbomber: Which is your new computer?
Lazysloth: this is new comp
prakyath_kantharaju: razer
aerotone: his trajectory is prolly fucked up, u might have moved him so he gets stuck
Caene: The ghost can't reach the set point
fuuqtv: delete him
NotSnuffy: !specs
lightofhel1: go Jonny, go!
KeyboardOreos: Look at your instagram, so you're wealthy now ?
KeyboardOreos: looked*
ArcherCreatlol: make fortnite PogChamp
vtmr: monkaS
Caene: LUL
aerotone: speedrunning
the_best_russian_bear: 1 step - write game
Caene: Delete ghosts, beat the game, put ghosts back in again - ship it.
cIvIcbooks: this is front page twitch quality
the_best_russian_bear: 2 step - finish game
the_best_russian_bear: 4Head
aerotone: ghosts have collision you know
Lazysloth: i would just move him
undefined_behavi0r: what's that game?
cankoloz: Who is this guy PogChamp
th3_maj0r: Strategy game guys. 2k19 Starcraft
KeyboardOreos: NotLikeThis
drag0s92: 5 speed
JumpTwiice: speedrun PogChamp
codevisionary: this guy is geohot @cankoloz
lightofhel1: speedrun PogChamp
codevisionary: google him
Caene: Yeah, the collision is making it so that ghosts can't reach the set points. AI doesn't even know it's stuck. LUL
JumpTwiice: @codevisionary u didnt get the joke LUL
stathizzzz: Issue a run command
Caene: Damn ghosts!
cankoloz: @JumpTwiice LUL
th3_maj0r: Hack the game! Yeah!
codevisionary: what joke
codevisionary: ?
JumpTwiice: PepeLaugh
dorkmo: no clip
b_______________________b: ALL WRONG :(
Zepcon7: Why on windows?
cankoloz: He doesn't know PepeLaugh
siwySF: he lacks critical information PepeLaugh
JumpTwiice: han ved inte PepeLaugh
codevisionary: ^ toxic
b_______________________b: clint2
b_______________________b: damn it
julien9877: he is unaware PepeLaugh
Nameless770: Waypoints were added to group and then groups global position was changed.
Taddell: From making self driving cars to creating childrens games in unity?
drag0s92: :))
codevisionary: @Taddell exactly
codevisionary: @Taddell we're joking though, right?
codevisionary: @Taddell toxicity gets you banned
kevin99gh: hey @georgehotz RalpherZ
th3_maj0r: wait, toxic again?
JumpTwiice: LUL i dont know if this guy is a troll or if he's serious
JumpTwiice: @codevisionary
Taddell: Joke a joke...
th3_maj0r: No, I'm joking, I don't know why he banned u, probably he didn't understand
JanTSV: Heyy, whus Up?
NonTrivial778: @Taddell bro take it easy with george
CraftyGaming: Just came back, each of those ghosts are children of your "Enemies" object. Make sure enemies is at 0,0,0
kevin99gh: i cant wait for VR to be more popular...i wanna live in vr BibleThump
youngTrick: nice new crib
CraftyGaming: I have to go play softball
dorkmo: when vr doesnt make me feel like puking
youngTrick: white on white on white
kevin99gh: yay nom nom lunch CorgiDerp
th3_maj0r: ahahaha yeash so easy
drag0s92: 'eazyest game ever'
smurfd0: "who u gonna call?" ;)
osaidaz99: happy Ramadan
codevisionary: have you seen Ready Player One @kevin99gh ?
aerotone: NotLikeThis
drag0s92: that one is in tub ?
Ustunner: What’s good George
kevin99gh: @dorkmo they are fixing that...newer vr headset should be fine for u i think
kevin99gh: @codevisionary no
CoffeeD2: ready player one is pretty bad
codevisionary: ikr
cankoloz: @CoffeeD2 I think it's average
codevisionary: at least we agree on something
kevin99gh: i cant wait to sit in a giant forest near a river with rtx on in vr BibleThump
cIvIcbooks: OOOO
Caene: PogChamp
Lazysloth: YOU MADE IT!
kevin99gh: prooo
cankoloz: PogChamp
youngsachi: PogChamp
drag0s92: circR circR circCosy circAmazing circAmazing circAmazing circAmazing circAmazing circAmazing
UniversalGeneve: LUL twitchies
Caene: Great journey!
siwySF: sound was 10 hours
dorkmo: heyguys100
JanTSV: when are u joining dem?
JanTSV: tsm
Jewishrambo: BibleThump ending?
Bloodspark_: @kevin99gh same about vr BibleTump
knilecrack: nice
Dsplits: you should do a music production stream
codevisionary: LUNCH @georgehotz
drag0s92: circLewd
Johnnymamen: l a u n c h
Bloodspark_: ANYWAYS PepeHands ?
th3_maj0r: TSM is a professional gaming team
Caene: Lunch and rant PogChamp
Ustunner: Go smoke
stathizzzz: Now lets break Android kernel PogChamp
markovchain21: use AI to make beats/music ?=
vtmr: sound engineer PogChamp
Caene: Sound is overrated 🔇
drag0s92: what laptop is is ?
kevin99gh: george needs to be in the vr/ ar industry
th3_maj0r: Razor 15 2k19
drag0s92: it is*
purpbroccoli: How's the keyboard?
Dsplits: what are you working on now?
drag0s92: thx
cIvIcbooks: are you going to use the headset camera to slam the user environ?
zneel_73: no more python tmux coding?
Caene: How is the keyboard on the Blade 15? They look sleek and the hardware seems fine for a laptop
kevin99gh: mod me?
th3_maj0r: Now u can swipe up on instagram right?
pikkuuu: I just don't like doing dev stuff on Windows for some reason
Ustunner: You a millionaire yet
th3_maj0r: You can link the stream on your stories
sharpblade95: bye
JumpTwiice: PogChamp
UniversalGeneve: bone induction headsets
kevin99gh: omg im happy
kevin99gh: geo headset
dorkmo: showlove1000
kevin99gh: hype
pikkuuu: LUL
zneel_73: LUL
Caene: LUL
vtmr: LUL
youngsachi: LUL
showzennn: LUL
kanogger: LUL
JanTSV: LUL
kevin99gh: we need ar using the power of the cloud
vtmr: 4Head
salamifred: LuL
zneel_73: LUL
kevin99gh: ez money
funwayz: MOST OF LUL
julien9877: how dare they!
tacorising3: LOL
yungosk: LUL
pikkuuu: just keep the money 4Head
julien9877: pay em in equity xqcM
codevisionary: I would work for you for free @georgehotz
codevisionary: hire me
drag0s92: i do love you bro, no homo! how can i make my money ur money ?
Lazysloth: just don't pay em duh
Dsplits: how do you expect to grow a company without employees?
BookRaider: is comma ai gone? what?
MalhadiJr: why the font rendering look awful ?
showzennn: you making headsets? really? what a waste lol
simon8162: You get paid in exposure
dorkmo: psy them in AR headsets
th3_maj0r: You can't make more money with hacking? lol
dicapriyo: so it all boils down to money 🤔
codevisionary: I'll be your employee for free @georgehotz
pikkuuu: ez money PogChamp
cankoloz: @georgehotz show the headset :)
JanTSV: high voice = real shit
JanTSV: LUL
kevin99gh: when do u see ar replace phones
dicapriyo: Kappa
vtmr: Kappa
cankoloz: Kappa
youngsachi: Kappa
nestradalink2: if
put_your_money_on_me: CoolStoryBob
dicapriyo: PogChamp
julien9877: LUL
aiis: Please give us 60 pixels per degree headsets @georgehotz
pikkuuu: CoolStoryBob
drag0s92: circClap circClap circClap circPaid circPaid circPaid circPaid circPaid circPaid
Lazysloth: magic leap is shit
showzennn: making headsets is about moving the world forward and not money Kappa
dorkmo: 2 burgedubais
th3_maj0r: I think this AR is too small btw, anyone else think the same?
codevisionary: the problem is that they have a professional website, and you don't @georgehotz (hire me for free)
julien9877: wtf
MDSZilla: 0
Dsplits: lol barely
aerotone: 2000
Lazysloth: they are giving them away
siwySF: more than 2
youngsachi: 1
Dsplits: is magic leap a public company?
julien9877: JUST 790M LUL
Dsplits: @georgehotz the point is taking the company public.. that's when youll get the return
Dqyijote: u only talk about money bro
MDSZilla: So they raise money but dont deliver?
UniversalGeneve: LUL
UniversalGeneve: RIP elizabeth
Zasuslive: George I see u making awesome software for this AR headset/platform.. but ergonomics, build quality, mass production etc don’t seem like your thing
funwayz: comma ai 8.1m
Zasuslive: Maybe that shit comes later
zneel_73: do you recommend for niche startup to raise money ?
emilwallin: Mästare
UniversalGeneve: it's not that she didn't deliver, she FAKED everything, which is worse
Dsplits: theranos was the biggest scam
MDSZilla: That's a total scam then wow.
JimsGlock: !playlist
pandatastisch9: i wish i would be smart
th3_maj0r: Commaai 8 milions? not a lot
pandatastisch9: will nsi-189 fix my brain?
aerotone: 300 comma ai's PogChamp
aerotone: I M A G I N E
MDSZilla: What ever you spend your investment is to grow if you dont then it dies true.
P0LY: LUL
JanTSV: does that mean 300 geohotzs??
lpdon2: why did he dump the macbook pro?
zneel_73: do you think that there is still place for new social network startups?
dicapriyo: i thought elon musk bootstraped tesla once Kappa
kevin99gh: i hope nintendo next console will be vr only followed by playstation 6 vr RalpherZ
cIvIcbooks: those valuations depend on litigating the fuck out of their ip not producing value
youngsachi: LUL
Dsplits: why a headset company?
funwayz: scam is everywhere
JanTSV: @dsplits why Not?
jamesred2313: Big difference between we have this and we Don't have this
Zasuslive: Headsets kinda make sense as the next step after phones
Dsplits: you should start a company that builds tools for the financial industry
kevin99gh: im a communist RalpherZ
stathizzzz: HOw much money did Elon offer you? Why reject him?
codevisionary: they had separate visions @stathizzzz
Zasuslive: Bro now your talking about other stuff pls talk about the simulation briefly an update since your talk
cankoloz: Iphone DansGame
kevin99gh: @zasuslive respect mr hots BibleThump
drag0s92: romania - the same thing
Sun__G: software communism is good for security though LUL
siwySF: jonh lemon dev became communist? LUL
emilwallin: Overpriced
stathizzzz: Id be happy with an alternating vision provided the money is good
youngsachi: LUL
pikkuuu: that's what a communist would say Kappa
knilecrack: communisam forces you to share
enzozordan: how long have you been working on this? (vr)
Sun__G: free software is the most successful implementation of communism Keepo
BiszkopTT: what do you think about slavoj zizek? Kappa
JanTSV: @knilecrack nah
knilecrack: yeah
Dsplits: so you're not going to raise money for your new company?
kevin99gh: communism= vr chat for ne
julien9877: I AM not A COMMUNIST
julien9877: Kappa
kevin99gh: me
codevisionary: most people don't even know what communism means
ssssimba: all about illusion
aerotone: how can i short this shit?
stathizzzz: Dont talk about communism, CIA is watching...
o_sagga: thoughts on bitcoin?
knilecrack: but there is nothing wrong with the ideology it's the people
funwayz: i was born in USSR LUL
aerotone: how can i short magic leap
smurfd0: isnt it always like that when new tech appears.. people pretend to have stuff for sale...
Dsplits: they are not public
aerotone: ill just short the current market then LUL
aerotone: tech bubble 2
aiis: which doesn't work if tech in general overachieves...like he said
Zasuslive: @kevin99gh was I being disrespectful?
hardtarget4: lol
kevin99gh: im joking @zasuslive lol
stathizzzz: Uber going down due to automation
Zasuslive: My bad lol
Dsplits: uber is going bankrupt in the next few years
julien9877: PepeLaugh oh no no no
JumpTwiice: why did it plump
austin_1_2: I think Uber’s Ipo is at a better price thang Lyft
vtmr: BOGGED
aerotone: have u seen beyond burger IPO price? holy shit what a short steal LOL
JumpTwiice: poomp eet
Dsplits: @georgehotz start a hedge fund
julien9877: 📉
Dsplits: no no please tell us
JumpTwiice: PepeLaugh 👉 📉
julien9877: finance is just a funnel scheme
Frogtech_: kaceyThink
pikkuuu: hedge funds etc. are not about creating value, if somebody actually believes that they're crazy, they're about making money for the the people running the fund naturally
undefined_behavi0r: traditionally the "value" of finance is providing liquidity: allocating capital where it is most needed. (However I agree that modern finance has strayed far from the ideal)
Zasuslive: Entropy :o
JanTSV: Change title to: learning economy on my new computer
pikkuuu: dab PogChamp
aerotone: hedge funds create jobs tho Kappa
tkslots: @georgehotz would you prefer freelancing to salary career?
JumpTwiice: KKona
stathizzzz: That applies to software too
julien9877: PogChamp
kevin99gh: @georgehotz should debate destiny RalpherZ
pikkuuu: KKona wealth you say
strippersncoke: would you see AWS as an example of this? @georgehotz
JumpTwiice: PogChamp
Dany4k: 5Head
stathizzzz: Destiny is a crook, geo is the real thing
hardtarget4: hardtarget4 subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months!
ssssimba: what are your thoughts about google keynote
P0LY: kurzweil 2029 monkaS
mikeyyinspace: Oil? KKona
MDSZilla: So a business that allows more buisness to depend on that buisness to run
Kustex: just joined, are you talking about the coming singularity???
Dsplits: Would you ever work for a company again?
the_middle: what about AR? Did u finish lemon?
eyep1e: budge phones before headsets
Kustex: PogChamp
cankoloz: Why do you thing google is gross
zneel_73: can u recommend good books to read? related to business
eyep1e: budget
cankoloz: think*
o_sagga: why?
stathizzzz: Amazon is the new hype!!
o_sagga: which big company you recommend? Microsoft?
lefg7: where do they A players work nowadays ?
aerotone: @georgehotz is it time to short the tech bubble 2?
P0LY: a/b/c? what does it mean
Blizzie: what do you think of the new microsoft terminal ?
meridiansis: ceilingboob
JanTSV: YouTube is buggy af
Caene: @P0LY Skill grade.
deadpool_reynolds: @P0LY good/normal/retard
MDSZilla: Amazon still isnt in my country so it provides no value to me LUL
kevin99gh: i want a vr headset with 8k per eyes using 2 hdmi 2.1 cables n 2 pcs MrDestructoid
Dsplits: But amazon has a lot more b and c players than google
littlebighead82: @georgehotz what are things that you consider a scam that society does not
KAZERKE: LIVE moon2POGGYWOGGY
o_sagga: @MDSZilla AWS
aerotone: amazon is in every country, prime on the other hand
MDSZilla: Not in mine
Dsplits: But ads provide value to company
Caene: So true LUL
aerotone: where do you live? iraq lol?
hubabuba1243: I love amazon
th3_maj0r: But amazon uses his warehouse workers as slaves
MDSZilla: Somewhere on planet earth Kappa
escapd: doenst google provide value to you?
Caene: Microsoft is smart. They set a low bar, so that any minor improvement is hype.
o_sagga: @MDSZilla you're benefiting from AWS, doesn't have to be in your country
aiis: not real 8k
Caene: LUL
thirteenn: wouldnt ads probide value to you if they're targeted correctly?
hubabuba1243: I buy stuff on amazon all the time
Sun__G: @georgehotz thoughts on social purpose as a company form? (like purism)
MDSZilla: @o_sagga I guess.
o_sagga: @MDSZilla Also Twitch :D
Dsplits: google provides value with android
ssssimba: Do you think google could ever be controlled by any rules in the future, when AI become big enough to be scary?
tkslots: @georgehotz will you create the first 4d environment? :D
Sun__G: why do you think its hypocrisy?
MDSZilla: @o_sagga Oh yes ofc :)
minmaxy: as an amazon employee, i'm not sure about the assessment, google still has the top talent afaik
Kustex: how many % of your worth is in bitcoin?
smurfd0: .. or googles slave ;)
KAZERKE: LUL
dunehazard: LUL
youngsachi: LUL
MDSZilla: Loads of videos about people quitting google on youtube itself LUL
Alpasfly: wait, are you using windows??
stathizzzz: Android has led mobile industry a decade back, due to bad implementation decisions and adoptions
Jakobo06: im guessing you dont like fb too :p
Blizzie: dont be evil OMEGALUL
notpikrua: Probably Netflix is #1
kevin99gh: cant believe oculus quest require a phone just for initial setup wtf
KAZERKE: quitting Google is profitable because of the 1M view YouTube video you can make out of it LUL
stathizzzz: Kotlin is much better implementation wise and platform independent wise
Dsplits: so facebook definitely provides no value
deR_Ed: clean coal, clean oil
Dimendz: A players are doing their own thing for the most part
cIvIcbooks: big companies with shittons of cash demonstrate the lack of ideas to reinvest their capital
zneel_73: netflix only recruit seniors
JumpTwiice: HeyGuys
drope77: byee
austin_1_2: Only reason why Facebook is still a thing is Instagram
drope77: love u
JanTSV: bye
rushd0wn23: thank you!
o_sagga: byeee :( love u
zneel_73: bb
kevin99gh: bye we love u
dicapriyo: bye
breadobtainer: tata
Dsplits: later
Caene: Good stream @georgehotz!
KAZERKE: I just arrived moon2PH
Alpasfly: besides netflix doesn't really do that much in terms of adding features
deadpool_reynolds: C You
tanoshiizo: hediHi bye
UneekPlayer: Bye
Sun__G: Kappa /
cIvIcbooks: <3
tacorising3: thanks geo
stathizzzz: BB
BiszkopTT: later my guy
Caene: Bye bye <3
emilwallin: Bye
o_sagga: BB
baxteriia: byee
slimyoof: take care george KonCha
BiszkopTT: <3
Zasuslive: Talk simulation
o_sagga: <3
qlo_sca: budiHI
Zasuslive: Pls
tanoshiizo: bye char KonCha
tanoshiizo: chat*
treestompztv: <3
mikeyyinspace: @austin_1_2 do you realize what you just said?
Raritetus: i definitely need more